(ROARING)
ANNOUNCER: The world of
investing can be a jungle.
Bulls. Bears.
Danger at every turn.
That's why we at Stratton
Oakmont
pride ourselves on being the
best.
Trained professionals to guide
you
through the financial
wilderness.
Stratton Oakmont.
Stability.
Integrity.
Pride.
(ROARING)
PEOPLE: (SHOUTING) One!
Two!
Three!
(ALL CHEERING)
Twenty-five grand to the first
cocksucker
to nail a bull's-eye!
(ALL CHEERING)
Come on! Let's go!
ALL: One!
Two!
Three!
JORDAN: My name is Jordan
Belfort.
Not him.
Me. That's right.
I'm a former member of the
middle class
raised by two accountants
in a tiny apartment in Bayside,
Queens.
The year I turned 26,
as the head of my own brokerage
firm,
I made $49 million,
which really pissed me off
because
it was three shy of a million a
week.
(UPBEAT BLUES MUSIC PLAYING)
No, no, no. My Ferrari was
white,
like Don Johnson's in Miami
Vice. Not red.
See that humongous estate down
there?
That's my house.
ROBIN LEACH: (OVER TV)
For millionaires whose ships...
JORDAN: My wife, Naomi,
the Duchess of Bay Ridge,
Brooklyn,
a former model and Miller Lite
girl.
Yeah.
She was the one with my cock
in her mouth in the Ferrari.
So put your dick back in your
pants.
In addition to Naomi and my two
perfect kids,
I own a mansion, private jet,
six cars, three horses,
two vacation homes, and a
170-foot yacht.
ROBIN LEACH: Anchors aweigh!
JORDAN: I also gamble like a
degenerate.
I drink like a fish.
I fuck hookers maybe five, six
times a week.
I have three different federal
agencies looking to indict me.
Oh, yeah, and I love drugs.
(FAINT CLANGING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay.
-One more round.
-Oh, yeah.
-Oh, you like it?
-Yeah.
Pull up. Pull up!
We're gonna crash, for Christ
sake!
JORDAN: Relax!
(SLURRING) Just relax.
(GROANING)
You okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
Good job.
You get in there safe, all
right?
Till the next time, brother.
Till next time.
Yup, on a daily basis
I consume enough drugs
to sedate Manhattan,
Long Island and Queens for a
month.
Okay, Mr. Jordan.
I take Quaaludes
10 to 15 times a day for my
"back pain,"
Adderall to stay focused,
Xanax to take the edge off,
pot to mellow me out,
cocaine to wake
me back up again and morphine,
well,
because it's awesome.
Good morning, Nathan.
But of all the drugs under God's
blue heaven,
there is one that is my absolute
favorite.
You see,
enough of this shit'll make you
invincible.
Able to conquer the world,
and eviscerate your enemies.
(SNORTS)
Ah!
And I'm not talking about this.
I'm talking about this.
See, money doesn't just buy you
a better life,
better food, better cars, better
pussy.
It also makes you a better
person.
You can give generously to the
church
or political party of your
choice.
You can save the fucking
spotted owl with money.
I always wanted to be rich. So
let me go back.
I'm 22 years old, newly married,
and already a money-crazed
little shit.
So what do I do?
I go to the one place
on Earth that befit my
high-minded ambitions.
I love you.
JERRY: You are lower than pond
scum.
You got a problem with that,
Jordan?
No. No problem at all.
Good. Because that is what you
are.
Pond scum.
Your job is connector,
which means that you'll
be dialing the phone over 500
times a day
trying to connect me
with wealthy business owners.
And until you pass your Series
7,
that is all you're gonna fucking
be doing. Sit.
Sit!
Now just so you know,
last year I made over $300,000.
The other guy you'll be working
for,
he made over a million.
JORDAN: A million dollars?
I could only imagine
what a douchebag that guy must
be.
Jordan Belfort.
Yes, sir.
-Mark Hanna.
-A pleasure to meet you.
And you as well.
I see you've already met the
village asshole.
Smile and dial.
And don't pick up
your fucking head until 1:00.
Hey, fuck him.
I'm the senior broker here.
He's just a worthless piker.
Why don't you blow me, Hanna?
Now did you really
pitch a stock in your job
interview?
I had to do something to stand
out.
Right, sir?
I fucking love that.
-Lunch. Today.
-Yeah.
We don't start dialing at 9:30
because our clients
are already answering the phone.
Three. Two. One.
Let's fuck!
(BELL RINGS)
JORDAN: You want to know
what money sounds like?
Go to a trading floor on Wall
Street.
"Fuck" this, "shit" that.
"Cunt," "cock," "asshole."
I couldn't believe
how these guys talked to each
other.
MAN 1: Good fucking package...
MAN 2: Piece of shit!
I was hooked in seconds.
It was like mainlining
adrenaline.
Yeah. Fuckface,
look at where the stock's at
today, huh?
You motherfucker, you can't get
any at 44...
-Pick up the cocksucking phone!
-Sorry...
You are such a fucking
douchebag, Hanna.
We don't give two shits
about how technology works
because all we care about
is getting fucking rich.
-Solid, 2,000.
-Jordan Belfort.
Done!
Time to paint the tape.
Whoo! 2,000. Microsoft. Going in
the hole!
Come on.
Live. Live. Hold on, that is
hot.
In. In. Shut that motherfucker.
Shut it! Shut it! Shut it!
Sold!
(MARK HUMMING)
(MARK POUNDING HIS CHEST)
Yeah.
(CONTINUES HUMMING)
Tootski?
Oh, no. Thank you, though.
Mr. Hanna, what can I bring for
you on this glorious afternoon?
Well, Hector, here's the game
plan.
You're gonna bring us two
Absolut martinis.
You know how I like them.
Straight up.
And then precisely
seven and one half minutes after
that,
you're gonna bring us two more.
Then two more after that every
five minutes
until one of us passes the fuck
out.
(CHUCKLES)
HECTOR: Excellent strategy, sir.
I'm good with water for now.
Thank you.
It's his first day on Wall
Street. Give him time.
-Thank you.
-Mmm-hmm.
Thank you.
Mr. Hanna?
You're able to do drugs during
the day
and then still function, still
do your job?
How the fuck else would you do
this job?
Cocaine and hookers, my friend.
Right. (CHUCKLES)
Well, I got to say, I'm
incredibly excited
to be a part of your firm. I
mean...
The clients you have are
absolutely...
Fuck the clients.
Your only responsibility
is to put meat on the table.
You got a girlfriend?
I'm married. I have a wife.
Her name is Teresa. She cuts
hair.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Think about Teresa.
Name of the game.
Move the money from
your client's pocket into your
pocket.
Right.
But if you make your clients
money at the same time,
it's advantageous to everyone.
Correct?
No.
Number one rule of Wall Street.
Nobody...
I don't care if you're Warren
Buffett
or if you're Jimmy Buffett.
Nobody knows if a stock is gonna
go up,
down, sideways, or in fucking
circles.
Least of all stockbrokers,
right?
It's all a fugazi. You know what
a fugazi is?
Fugayzi. It's a fake.
Fugayzi, fugazi,
it's a whazy, it's a woozy,
it's...
(WHISTLES) Fairy dust. It
doesn't exist.
It's never landed. It is no
matter.
It's not on the elemental chart.
It's not fucking real.
-Right?
-Right.
-Stay with me.
-Mmm-hmm.
We don't create shit. We don't
build anything.
No.
So if you got a client
who bought stock at eight
and it now sits at 16, he's all
fucking happy.
He wants to cash in, liquidate,
take his fucking money and run
home.
-You don't let him do that.
-Okay.
-'Cause that would make it real.
-Right.
No. What do you do?
You get another brilliant idea.
A special idea.
Another "situation." Another
stock
to reinvest his earnings and
then some.
And he will, every single time.
'Cause they're fucking addicted.
And you just keep doing this,
again and again and again.
Meanwhile, he thinks he's
getting shit rich,
which he is, on paper.
But you and me, the brokers,
we're taking home cold hard cash
via commission, motherfucker.
Right.
That's incredible, sir.
I can't tell you how excited I
am.
You should be.
There's two keys to success
in the broker business.
First of all...
(EXHALES)
You gotta stay relaxed.
Yeah.
Do you jerk off?
Do I... Do I jerk off?
Yeah. Yeah, I jerk off. Yeah.
How many times a week?
Like three or four.
Three or four times, maybe five.
Gotta pump those numbers up.
Those are rookie numbers in this
racket.
I myself, I jerk off at least
twice a day.
-Wow.
-Once in the morning
right after I work out,
then once right after lunch.
-Really?
-Mmm-hmm.
I want to. That's not why I do
it.
I do it 'cause I fucking need
to.
Think about it. You're dealing
with numbers.
All day long, decimal points,
high frequencies.
Bang, bang, bang.
(SQUEAKING)
Fucking digits.
All very acidic
above-the-shoulders mustard
shit.
-All right?
-Mmm-hmm.
It kind of wigs some people out.
-Right.
-Mmm-hmm.
You got to feed the geese
to keep the blood flowing.
I keep the rhythm below the
belt.
Done.
This is not a tip, this is a
prescription.
-Trust me.
-Mmm-hmm.
If you don't, you will fall out
of balance,
split your differential and tip
the fuck over.
Or worse yet,
I've seen this happen, implode.
No, I don't want to implode,
sir.
No. No, you don't.
I'm in it for the long run, you
know?
-Implosions are ugly.
-Yeah.
Pop off to the bathroom,
work one out any time you can.
When you get really good at it,
you'll fucking be stroking it
and you'll be thinking about
money.
Second key to success in this
racket
is this little baby right here.
It's called cocaine.
Right.
It'll keep you sharp between the
ears.
It'll also help your fingers
dial faster.
And guess what?
That's good for me.
Yes, sir.
Revolutions. You follow?
Revolutions.
Keep the clients on the Ferris
wheel.
And it goes. The park is open
24/7, 365,
every decade, every goddamn
century.
-That's it.
-(JORDAN LAUGHING)
The name of the game.
Halkidiki?
-Mmm.
-Thank you.
(MARK HUMMING)
Come on.
(BOTH HUMMING)
We're the common denominator.
Ah!
BOTH: Ah!
Keep it up for me.
[S](SINGING) You've seen the
echo
[S] And the money comes in
[S] The parade comes to town
[S] Going down Broadway
[S] It's a one-way street
[S] Whichever way I go
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
JORDAN: The next six months,
I got to know the ins and outs
of Wall Street.
Earning shit money
as I geared up to take my Series
7.
Oh!
Oh, fuckers.
Then I was a licensed broker at
last,
ready to make my fortune.
My first day as a future Master
of the Universe.
I have Exxon at 86 1/4 six
months ago.
Today it is trading at 36 1/2.
Mr...
JORDAN: They called it Black
Monday.
No shit.
By 4:00 p.m., the market
had dropped 508 points.
The biggest plummet since the
crash of '29.
MARK: I know your family, you
know mine.
No, I don't know.
Some fucking country in Europe
took a shit.
Let them do what they want to
fucking do.
Our market's solid.
This is not something that you
want to sell.
You know what happened?
A fucking tsunami.
I think you're making a big
mistake.
Yes, I will talk to your wife.
MARK: Trust me, do not answer
the phone.
A lot of people are gonna be
calling you,
trying to get your dirty
laundry.
We don't know what's going on
here.
I know. I know.
(BELL RINGS)
MARK: Holy
fucking shit!
JORDAN: Unbelievable.
My first shitty day as a broker.
Within a month, L.F. Rothschild,
an institution since 1899,
closed its doors.
Wall Street had swallowed me up
and shit me right back out
again.
We could pawn my engagement ring
if we needed to.
-Babe...
-Because I don't mind.
If we needed to, I'm saying...
-Will you listen to me?
-Okay.
You're not pawning anything.
Okay?
-Okay.
-What do I always tell you?
You're gonna be a millionaire.
That's right. Okay? Just let me
look.
We'll find something.
-How about this?
-What?
Nobody Beats the Wiz, the
electronics store.
Stock boy. What do you think?
You're not gonna work at that
place.
Yeah, but, you know, you start
off...
Jordan, you're gonna be
miserable at that place
-if you go there.
-I know.
It's sales. You work your way
up,
you'll be a general manager.
-You're not gonna be a stock
boy.
-Why not?
'Cause you're a stockbroker.
You understand that
nobody's hiring stockbrokers
right now?
You understand that?
Okay?
(JORDAN SIGHS)
Ah. This place is.
-What?
-What's that say?
"Stockbrokers."
(LAUGHS)
In Long Island?
-Stockbrokers in Long Island?
-Yeah.
TERESA: It's in Long Island. So
what?
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
Hey, I'm looking for Investor's
Center.
What's that? You want to invest?
No. Investor's Center.
I'm looking for Investor's
Center.
Yeah, yeah, that's us. Hey. This
is it. This is it.
-I'm Dwayne. Yeah.
-You're Dwayne?
Hi, Dwayne. We spoke on the
phone.
I'm Jordan Belfort.
I'm the broker from Rothschild
in New York.
Yes, yeah. Have a seat. How are
you?
We had a conversation...
We spoke on the phone earlier,
right?
-Two hours ago.
-Right.
Yeah.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
They're up and comers.
That's what that means.
It's three cents a share, that's
$3!
You cheap fuck!
So...
So where are your Quotrons here?
-Quotrons?
-Yeah. Your computers.
No, no. We don't even need
computers here.
We just trade right off the pink
sheets here.
-Pink sheets?
-Yeah, they're penny stocks.
You know, companies that
can't get listed on NASDAQ,
they don't have enough capital?
Their shares trade here.
-Penny stocks?
-Yeah.
This one, Aerodyne, is a really
interesting...
Or Aerotyne...
Aerotyne, yeah.
Aero... Aerotyne...
Aerotyne. Yeah.
Very hot stock right now.
Oh, yeah?
They're just a couple
of brothers that are making
radar detectors out of their
garage.
They're out in Dubuque.
Maybe it's microwaves. I'm not
sure.
But you call the company's main
line,
their mom, Dorothy, answers
and she is so sweet.
-Good company.
-I actually don't know what else
to...
I don't know anything else
about them other than that.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Six cents a share?
Hey, come on. Who buys this
crap?
Well, I mean...
Honestly, mostly schmucks.
Postmen, there's always postmen.
Plumbers.
They see our ads in
the back of Hustler and Popular
Mechanics.
Our ads actually say they can
get rich quick.
-Hustler?
-Yeah.
You know, those girlie
magazines.
Yeah, yeah. Nudie mag.
-A lot.
-Yeah.
We're helping them finance
houses,
we're helping them
buy their wife a diamond ring...
A boat maybe.
Is this...
Is this stuff regulated or are
you guys...
What are you doing here?
Uh...
Sort of.
Sort of?
Jesus Christ, the spread on
these is huge.
Yeah. And that's the point,
that's...
What's your name again?
Mine... Jordan Belfort.
Jordan, what do you get
on that blue chip stock?
I make one percent.
Or I did make one percent.
Pink sheets, it's 50.
It's 50%?
50% commission?
-Yup.
-For what?
It's our markup for our
services.
And so if I... If I...
If I sell a stock at $10,000,
my commission is 5,000 bucks?
If you sell $10,000 worth of
this stock,
I will personally give you a
blowjob for free.
(LAUGHS)
And I hope it happens.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
JORDAN: Hello, John,
how are you doing today?
You mailed in my company
a postcard a few weeks back
requesting information on penny
stocks
that had huge upside potential
with very little downside risk.
-Does that ring a bell?
-Yeah, I may have sent
something.
Okay, great.
The reason for the call today,
John, is,
something just came across my
desk, John.
It is perhaps the
best thing I've seen in the last
six months.
If you have 60 seconds, I'd like
to share
the idea with you. You got a
minute?
Actually, I'm really very...
The name of the company,
Aerotyne International.
It is a cutting edge
high-tech firm out of the
Midwest
awaiting imminent patent
approval
on the next generation of radar
detectors
that have both huge
military and civilian
applications now.
Right now, John,
the stock trades
over-the-counter at 10 cents a
share.
And by the way, John, our
analysts indicate
it could go a heck of a lot
higher than that.
Your profit on a mere $6,000
investment would be upwards of
$60,000!
Jesus! That's my mortgage, man.
Exactly. You could pay off your
mortgage.
This stock will pay off my
house?
John, one thing I can promise
you,
even in this market,
is that I never ask my clients
to judge me on my winners.
I ask them to judge me on my
losers
because I have so few.
And in the case of Aerotyne,
based on every
technical factor out there,
John,
we are looking at a grand slam
home run.
Okay, let's do it. I'll do four
grand.
$4,000? That'd be 40,000 shares,
John.
Let me lock in that trade right
now
and get back to you with my
secretary
with an exact confirmation.
Sound good, John?
-Yeah, sounds good.
-Great.
Hey, John.
Thank you for your vote of
confidence.
And welcome to the Investor's
Center.
Yeah, thanks a lot, man.
Bye-bye.
How'd you fucking do that?
(MAN LAUGHS)
JORDAN: Just like that, I made
two grand.
The other guys looked at me
like I'd just discovered fire.
Great! Even better!
I was selling garbage to garbage
men
and making cash hand over fist.
The only problem you're gonna
have is that you didn't buy
more.
Boom shocka locka!
-So I was selling them shit.
-(EXCLAIMS IN SPANISH)
But the way I looked at it,
their money was better off in my
pocket.
I knew how to spend it better.
DONNIE: Excuse me.
Is that your car in the lot?
JORDAN: Yeah.
-It's a nice ride.
-Thanks, man.
Donnie Azoff.
Hey. I'm Jordan Belfort.
-Nice to meet you.
-How you doing?
You know, actually, I see that
car around.
-I see it around a lot.
-Oh, yeah, where?
I think we live in the same
building.
-No shit?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Twelfth floor?
-Yeah. What floor are you on?
Fourth floor.
-I have two little kids. Ugly
wife.
-Right.
(LAUGHS)
What do you do, bro?
What do you mean, what do I do?
For work, what do you do?
I'm a stockbroker.
-Stockbroker?
-Yeah.
Children's furniture.
Oh, good for you.
It's all right.
You make a lot of money?
Yeah, I do all right for myself.
I'm trying to put it together.
You got your fucking nice car,
we live in the same building. I
just...
I'm not understanding...
How much money do you make?
I don't know. $70,000 last
month.
Get the fuck...
Get the fuck out of here.
No, I'm serious.
Yeah, no, I'm serious, too.
Seriously, how much money do you
make?
I told you. $70,000.
Well, technically, $72,000.
Last month. Something like that.
You made 72 grand in one month?
Yeah.
I'll tell you what.
You show me a pay stub for
$72,000 on it,
I quit my job right now and I
work for you.
DONNIE: Hey, Paulie, what's up?
No, yeah, yeah. No, everything's
fine.
Hey, listen, I quit.
JORDAN: And he did quit his job.
Which I thought was a little
weird.
I mean, I just met this fucking
guy.
Don't fucking tell Susan.
It's none of her business.
There were other things about
him, too.
Like his phosphorescent white
teeth.
...wife! I gotta fucking deal
with your wife?
The fact that he wore
horn rims with clear lenses
just to look more WASP-y.
And then, there were these
rumors.
I heard some stupid shit. I
don't know.
Fuck, I didn't even want to
bring it up.
It's just...
-It's stupid.
-Shit with me?
You know, people say shit. I
don't even know.
I don't even listen to it half
the time.
What are they saying?
Shit about you
and your cousin or something
like that.
I don't even listen to it.
Bro, it's not like that.
It's not like that.
Like you married your cousin
or some stupid shit. No?
Yeah, my wife. Yeah.
My wife is my cousin, or
whatever.
But it's not like what you
think,
or whatever, you know.
Is she like a first cousin, or
is she...
Yeah, no, she's, you know...
Her... Her father
is the brother of my mom.
It's not like, what... You know.
Look, we grew up together.
And she grew up hot, you know.
She fucking grew up hot.
And all my friends
were trying to fuck her, you
know.
And I'm not gonna let someone...
You know,
one of these assholes fuck my
cousin,
so, you know,
I used the cousin thing as like
an in with her.
I'm not gonna let
someone else fuck my cousin.
You know, if anyone's gonna fuck
my cousin,
it's gonna be me, out of
respect. You know?
No, I get it. Yeah.
I mean, you're not afraid of
like the whole kid thing, right?
-What? Having kids with her?
-Yeah.
No. We have two kids.
And they're... I mean...
I don't want to get personal,
but they're okay?
No, they're not retarded or
anything like that.
But there's a big chance, right,
if...
Yeah, there's like a 60%, you
know,
60 to 65% chance the kid's gonna
be
fucking retarded or whatever.
That'd scare the shit out of me,
buddy.
Look, man, a lot of having a
kid,
or whatever, takes risk,
whether you're fucking cousins
or not.
What if something like that
happened?
Basically, you know, if the kid
was retarded,
I would, you know, drive it up
to the country
and just, like, you know,
open the door and say,
"You're free now." You know,
like, "Run free."
You know?
You're completely fucking with
me.
(LAUGHS)
That's horrible. You're not
gonna...
You look like you've... No.
We would take it to, like,
an institution or somewhere
that's handled to,
like, you know, raise the kid or
whatever.
You know what?
If you're happy, God bless you,
buddy.
No, I'm not fucking happy.
No one who's married is fucking
happy.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that,
buddy.
Listen, I'm really, you know...
I'm really appreciative for this
fucking job.
I'm really enjoying it.
I'm really happy with what
you're doing.
Actually, I got you a little
present.
-You got me a present?
-I got you something.
Oh, fuck. You're sweet.
Yeah. It's in the back though.
-What do you mean?
-You gotta go out back.
Like it's wrapped up or
something?
It's wrapped up. Yeah.
-I don't get it.
-Neither do I.
Let's fucking go. Come on.
Your turn.
I'm not fucking doing this.
You're out of your fucking mind.
-Smoke this shit, bro.
-No.
No one's fucking here, bro.
Get the fuck...
Fucking smoke crack with me,
bro.
I'm not fucking doing it.
Smoke crack.
Smoke some fucking crack with
me, bro.
One hit. One hit. That's it.
Okay.
Fucking nut job.
(MOANS)
Wow!
(LAUGHING)
Wow.
Let's go run, huh?
We gotta get out of here, buddy.
We gotta get out of here. Let's
go fucking run.
Let's run like
we're fucking lions and tigers
and bears!
Let's run! Let's fucking run!
Let's fucking run! Go!
Go, go, go, go!
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
MAN: You've reached Frank's Best
Auto Body.
We're closed right now.
So please leave us a message.
JORDAN: Hello. My name is Jordan
Belfort.
My partner and I
are very interested in renting
out your garage.
Donnie and I were going out on
our own.
And the first thing we needed
was brokers.
Guys with sales experience.
So I recruited some of my
hometown boys.
Sea Otter, who sold meat and
weed.
Chester, who sold tires and
And Robbie, who sold anything
he could get his hands on.
Mostly weed.
Can you bring me some ketchup?
Okay?
This is Brad.
And Brad's the guy I really
wanted.
But he didn't go along with us.
He was already making
so much money selling Quaaludes,
he'd become the Quaalude king of
Bayside.
Getting any pussy with that
thing or what?
Yeah, man, of course.
Bring some of them chicks
around here sometime, huh?
Let 'em watch.
Let 'em watch. Know what I mean?
Hey, Zip!
You tell your sister I was
asking about her.
Why don't you bring me a pair of
her panties next time you come
through.
Yeah, man. She said she don't
want to talk to you anymore,
man.
Get the fuck out of here.
Hey, Ma, we got chicken or what?
Ma!
JORDAN: You listening?
It's easier than you think.
Every person you're on the phone
with,
they want to get rich
and they want to get rich
quickly.
They all want something for
nothing.
There was this one time
that I was selling pot to this
Amish dude.
You know those guys who got like
the beard
with like no mustache or some
bullshit?
Well, he says that he only
wants to make furniture.
I don't understand.
CHESTER: What's that got to
do with anything?
What the fuck are you talking
about?
I'm not putting words
in your mouth or nothing,
but you just said that
everybody wants to get rich.
Holy fuck, you did just say
that.
What the fuck are you talking
about?
Yeah, like Buddhists.
They don't give a shit about
money.
They're wrapped in sheets.
They're not buying shit.
I'm not talking about Buddhists
or Amish.
I'm talking about normal people,
working-class, everyday people.
Everyone wants to get rich. Am I
crazy?
There's no such thing as an
Amish Buddhist.
-I'm pretty fucking sure.
-There could be.
Can we get some ketchup, please?
Do you guys not want to make
money?
ALL: I want to make some money.
I want to make some fucking
money, okay.
I can sell anything.
Shit, I can sell ludes to a
convent full of nuns,
and get them so horny
they'd be fucking each other.
That's the attitude. You can
sell anything?
Sell me this fucking pen right
here.
You can sell anything. Sell
that. Go ahead.
Sell me the pen.
Can I finish eating first? I
haven't eaten today.
Brad, show them how it's done.
Boom.
Sell me that pen. Watch. Go on.
You want me to sell this fucking
pen?
That's my boy right there.
Can fucking sell anything.
Why don't you do me a favor.
Write your name down on that
napkin for me.
I don't have a pen.
Exactly. Supply and demand, my
friend.
-Holy shit.
-See what I'm saying?
He's creating urgency.
Get them to want to buy the
stock.
Convince them it's something
they need,
you know what I mean?
And that's the thing.
All nuns are lesbians.
What the fuck are you talking
about, Otter?
OTTER: Think about it.
They can't keep a dude
so they're gonna start fucking
chicks.
Four fucking times, Kimmie! Four
times.
NICKY: He's not with us.
ROBBIE: Friggin' Rambo.
Now she runs.
JORDAN: But look.
I knew these guys weren't like
Harvard MBAs.
Robbie Feinberg, the pinhead,
took five years to finish high
school.
Alden Kupferberg,
the Sea Otter, didn't even
graduate.
Chester Ming, the depraved
Chinaman,
thought jujitsu was in Israel.
Smartest of the bunch was Nicky
Koskoff.
He actually went to law school.
I called him Rugrat
because of his piece of shit
hairpiece.
Still, give them to me
young, hungry and stupid
and in no time, I'll make them
rich.
TERESA: Oh, my God.
Jordan, that...
You like it, baby?
Oh, my God, it's beautiful.
They're not the biggest stones
in the world,
but I promise they're really
high quality.
It's beautiful.
They're so beautiful.
Oh, boy.
What?
I know that look. What is it? Go
ahead.
I don't know, it's... You
know...
These stocks... These
companies...
They're like crappy companies.
-Well, yeah.
-Okay.
Yeah, they're terrible.
Don't worry about it. I told
you,
what I'm doing is completely
legal.
Yeah, I know.
But they're not gonna make
anyone money though, right?
Well, sometimes they do,
sometimes they don't.
You know how it goes.
Wouldn't you feel better
if you sold that stuff to rich
people
who can, like, afford to lose
all that money?
Of course.
But rich people don't buy penny
stocks.
They just don't.
Why not?
JORDAN: Because
they're too smart, that's why
not.
I mean, what person with a
college education
would trust this bunch of
jerk-offs?
Hang up the phone.
Tell him you'll call him back.
I got five fucking grand
on the phone right now!
DONNIE: Hey!
But what if they didn't sound
like a bunch of jerk-offs?
What if I could teach them
how to sell to people with
money?
Real money.
So I decided to reinvent the
company.
Gentlemen, welcome
to Stratton Oakmont.
You schnooks will now be
targeting
the wealthiest 1% of Americans.
We're talking about whales here.
Moby fucking Dicks.
And with this script,
which is now your new harpoon,
I'm gonna teach each and every
one of you
to be Captain fucking Ahab.
Get it? Huh?
Captain who?
Captain Ahab. From the
fucking...
The book, motherfucker. From the
book.
Turn your fucking brain on.
-Fuck you.
-Jesus fuck, Robbie.
JORDAN: Listen to me.
We're a new company with a new
name.
A company that our clients can
believe in.
trust.
A firm whose roots
are so deeply embedded into Wall
Street
that our very founders
sailed over on the Mayflower
and chiseled the name Stratton
Oakmont
right into Plymouth fucking
Rock!
-You got it?
-(ALL CHUCKLING)
What we're gonna do is this.
First we pitch 'em Disney,
AT&T, IBM, blue chip stocks
exclusively.
Companies these people know.
Once we've suckered them in,
we unload the dog shit.
The pink sheets,
the penny stocks, where we make
the money.
50% commission, baby.
Now the key to making money
in a situation like this
is to position yourself now
before the settlement.
Because by the time you read
about it
in The Wall Street Journal,
it's already too late.
Then you wait.
You wait.
And whoever speaks first loses.
CLIENT: Sorry...
I appreciate the call.
I really have to give this some
thought
and talk to my wife about it.
Can I call you back?
They don't know, right?
They gotta think about it,
they gotta talk to their fucking
wives,
or the fucking Tooth Fairy.
Point is, it doesn't matter
what the fuck they say.
The only real objection that
they have
is that they don't trust you
guys.
And why should they trust you?
I mean, look at you.
You're a bunch of fucking
sleazy salesmen, right?
(ALL LAUGHING)
So, what do you say?
You mean to tell me
that if I put you in at Union
Carbide at seven
and took you out at 32...
Texas Instruments at 11
and took you out at 47...
U.S. Steel at 16, took you out
at 41...
You wouldn't be saying
to me right now, "Chester,
"pick me up a few thousand
shares of Disney
"on the spot, right now. Come
on."
Honestly, Kevin? Honestly?
Seriously?
I don't know you.
You cold-called me. You're a
total stranger.
I am in complete agreement with
you.
You don't know me, I don't know
Let me introduce myself to you.
My name is Alden Kupferberg.
-Robbie Feinberg.
-Chester Ming.
I'm Senior Vice President
at Stratton Oakmont...
...and I plan on being one of
the...
...top brokers in my firm next
year.
And I'm not gonna get there
by being wrong, Stanley.
I do wanna say that you sound
like a...
You sound like a pretty sincere
guy.
-(LAUGHING)
-OTTER: It's not gonna make you
rich
and it's not gonna make you
poor.
But what this trade will do is
serve as...
...a benchmark for future
business, Kevin.
You feel comfortable with me
now, Scotty?
And then you'll know for sure
that you finally found a broker
on Wall Street
that you can trust,
and who can consistently make
you money.
Sound fair enough?
(MOUTHING)
You know what... Yeah.
I gotta say, I'm pretty
impressed.
What are you thinking?
Kevin.
You give me one shot here
on a blue chip stock like Kodak,
and believe me, Kevin,
the only problem you're gonna
have
is that you didn't buy more.
Sound fair enough?
Shit. My...
Uh...
(CHUCKLES)
My wife might divorce me, but...
Yeah, let's do it.
(ALL LAUGHING QUIETLY)
Excellent choice, Kevin.
How much do you want to go for
this time?
Let's do five... $5,000.
Can we try 8,000, Kevin?
All right. Let's do 10.
-Ten.
-You want to do that?
Excellent choice!
Kevin, let me lock in that trade
right now
and get back to you in a few
minutes
with an exact confirmation,
Kevin.
And welcome to Stratton Oakmont.
Thanks, man. I'm gonna have a
beer.
This is fun.
Take it easy, Kev.
Hey, thanks, Jordan. Thanks a...
Fuck that motherfucker!
That's what I'm talking about!
What a fucking idiot.
The one thing I know about
in this world is airlines.
And Cuchon Airlines is the
future of airlines.
Get in now or...
-I'm Nicky Koskoff...
-Chester Ming...
BOTH: ...and I'm a Senior Vice
President
with Stratton Oakmont.
Judy, I am so, so, so sorry for
your loss.
When did he pass?
Just say I'm wrong, right.
And the stock goes down a couple
points...
...and it makes you,
in the words of my grandfather,
God rest his soul, "A shit ton
of money."
It's like getting in on fucking
sunlight
before there was fucking
sunlight.
You understand?
MAN 1: Can we do 8,000 shares?
MAN 2: Okay, 25,000.
That's a very intelligent
decision.
I'm gonna transfer you to my
sales associate.
Rhonda!
-Rhonda!
-...put you through to Andrea.
Has anybody fucking seen Rhonda?
(BELL RINGING)
Everybody have a good week?
ALL: Yeah!
The end of the month.
$28.7 million in gross
commissions,
all from pink sheet stock, boys!
And to celebrate with
our weekly act of debauchery,
I have offered our lovely sales
assistant,
Danielle Harrison, here,
$10,000 to shave her fucking
head!
-(ALL CHEERING)
-Yeah!
(LAUGHING)
NICKY: Yeah, you want this?
You want this?
Let's scalp her! Scalp her!
NICKY: Let the scalping begin!
ALL: (CHANTING) Scalp! Scalp!
Scalp!
Scalp! Scalp! Scalp!
JORDAN: FYI, boys, Danielle has
promised
to use this $10,000 for breast
implants!
She's already got C cups,
but now she wants fucking double
D's!
Is this a great fucking company
or what?
Is this the greatest company in
the world?
Donnie!
Blow the roof off this
motherfucker!
(MARCHING BAND PLAYING)
Champagne?
Send in the stripees!
(ALL CHEERING)
Mine!
(YELLING)
JORDAN: Word about us spread
throughout Wall Street.
Even the places I didn't want it
to.
It wasn't long before Forbes
magazine,
the flagship of Wall Street,
called to do a profile on me.
Let me ask you, how do
you see the future for Stratton
Oakmont?
One word?
(EXHALES) Diversification.
Sounds good.
Thank you so much. I have more
than enough.
-I appreciate your time.
-Fantastic.
Can we get a quick picture?
(CAMERA CLICKS)
JORDAN: A total fucking hatchet
job.
This conniving little twat! Look
at this!
"The Wolf of Wall Street" they
call me. Look.
Your hair looks good.
-Well, my hair looks good.
-Yeah.
"Jordan Belfort,
sounding like a kind of twisted
Robin Hood
"who takes from the rich and
gives to himself
"and his merry little band of
brokers."
-Read that. Read it.
-Listen.
There is no such thing
as bad publicity, sweetheart.
Read the article, babe.
Jordan, you look great!
You're in a huge magazine.
Big fucking deal I look great.
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
MAN: Mr. Belfort! Can you
look at my resume, please?
Excuse me, excuse me, sir!
Calm the fuck down!
What the hell's all this?
It's the Forbes article.
They all want to work for you
now.
Hey! What did I say?
I'm just trying to be nice.
Hey, you want a job, you talk to
me!
-Mr. Belfort!
-Give me one minute.
JORDAN: Forbes made me a
superstar.
Every day, dozens of
money-crazed
kids beat a path to my door.
If we hired 'em, they
dropped straight out of college
overnight
and spent whatever allowance
they had
on a new suit from our Stratton
tailor.
Are you fucking serious right
now?
I mean, we were literally
putting clothes on these kids'
backs.
And here comes this jerk-off
sniffing around.
But, you know,
every time someone rises up in
this world,
there's always gonna be
some asshole trying to drag him
down.
Within months, we doubled in
size,
moved to even bigger offices.
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
It was a madhouse.
A greed-fest,
with equal parts cocaine,
testosterone, and body fluids.
(SCREAMING) Yes!
It got so bad,
I had to declare the office a
fuck-free zone
between the hours of 9:00 and
7:00.
But I'm telling you, even that
didn't help.
Actually, the madness started
on our very first day,
when one of our brokers, Ben
Jenner,
christened the elevator by
getting a blowjob
from a sales assistant.
Her name was Pam, and to her
credit,
she did have this amazing
technique,
with this wild twist and jerk
motion.
About a month later,
Donnie and I decided to
double-team her
on a Saturday afternoon
while our wives were
out shopping for Christmas
dresses.
Eventually, Ben married her,
which was pretty amazing
considering she blew
every single guy in the office.
Then he got depressed
and killed himself three years
later.
Anyway, I hired my dad, Max,
to maintain order as the
Enforcer.
Stratton's very own Gestapo.
We called him Mad Max
because of his hair-trigger
temper,
which could be set off by
something
as innocuous as a ringing
telephone.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Who the fuck has the goddamn
gall
to call this house on a Tuesday
night?
God damn it!
You're gonna miss it!
Oh, please, tell me something I
don't know.
I wait all week for the fucking
Equalizer
and they have to fucking...
Hello.
JORDAN: But as soon as
he picked up the phone...
Gene. How are you, Gene?
...he'd affect this weird
British accent.
Right-o, Gene, that'd be great.
Cheerio.
It was absolutely bizarre.
The fucking halfwit!
-He'd hang up...
-You missed it!
...and then he's Mad Max all
over again.
Damn it!
All right, tell me what
happened.
What happened?
Well, he discovered it was the
mother's sister.
Who's he? Who? Tell me who...
The main guy. You know who the
main...
The main guy...
It was his mother's sister.
She showed up dead.
(LAUGHING)
JORDAN: Of course,
Mad Max didn't have to know
everything we were doing at
Stratton.
And then there's a big target
and we...
They get launched at the target.
They stick.
NICKY: There's a bull's-eye
and the bull's-eye's a dollar
sign.
Whoever gets closer to the
dollar sign
gets the most points.
I'm gonna throw
the shit out of this little
fucking thing.
So if it gets hurt, what
happens?
'Cause we're gonna get fucking
nuts.
I don't think he's gonna get
hurt.
They're like...
They got like superhuman
strength.
I think he's gonna be fine.
You can't look him right in the
eyes.
You can't look him in the eye?
That's a fact. I saw it on PBS.
They get confused
and their wires get crossed.
You gotta look at their chin.
Like it looks like I'm looking
at you but I'm looking at your
chin.
I feel like you're addressing me
right now, but you're not, are
you?
They're like the Mona Lisa.
They find eye contact,
like, wherever you are standing
in the room.
And they lock in.
JORDAN: No, but there is
a limit to what we can do with
them?
We're allowed to throw shit at
'em.
We're allowed to throw food?
Bananas.
Any food. Correct.
But, for example, what I
wouldn't do is
maybe like tell him to pull his
cock out
and like get some of the girls
to, you know,
fondle him and shit like that.
That would be... That's
unacceptable?
Let's keep that in our back
pocket.
This guy is more about
throwing at the dartboard.
Correct. Yes, yes, yes.
The thing is, this is their
gift, okay.
They're built to be thrown like
a lawn dart.
They're top heavy like a lawn
dart.
So they're built for accuracy.
Oh, my God. Can we bowl with
this guy?
That's his fucking brother, Rob.
His brother's the bowling ball.
The brother, you put a
skateboard on him,
you strap him to a skateboard,
you toss him down an alley at
some pins.
-No shit. That's interesting.
-Swear to fucking God.
-Can we get that guy?
-Yeah, we'll get that guy, too.
But it says here this guy
will show his cock. Yeah.
-Instead of growing up. Yeah.
-JORDAN: He will?
They are very ornery by the way,
so you gotta be very careful
with these little guys.
Safety first.
Safety is first, all right?
I want somebody with
a fucking tranquilizer gun
ready to knock this fucker out.
-Do we want to get like a...
-Mace. Taser guns.
A pellet gun maybe?
No, a pellet gun is gonna hurt
him.
I just want him out. Knocked out
cold.
But I say we stick with the
loophole.
Right? Okay?
If we don't consider him a
human,
we just consider it an act,
I think we're in the clear.
Like The Flying Wallendas.
You know, a lot of those guys
died
but they never sued anybody.
The important thing
you guys gotta keep in mind
is that these things gossip.
They get together and they
gossip.
-That's a good point.
-And the last thing
that we need is them
getting together and saying,
"Oh, they made fun of us."
Like, it's gonna make Stratton
look bad.
That's why I love you.
You think of shit like that.
JORDAN: When they come in,
we treat it just like one of us.
Okay?
ALL: (CHANTING) One of us.
Gooble gobble, one of us.
We accept them, one of us!
We accept them, one of us.
Gooble gobble, one of us!
Jordan! Your dad's coming.
Something about the American
Express bill.
Can you get him out of here?
Yeah. Lick my twat.
No, I'm serious!
Fuck. Guys, act like we're
working.
You got any fucking stock forms?
He's coming, he's coming.
Make some shit up.
I think if we short Pfizer...
$430,000 in one month, Jordy,
huh?
Four hundred and fucking 30,000
fucking dollars in one fucking
month!
Good morning.
They're business expenses.
Relax.
MAX: Business expenses?
JORDAN: Yes.
-Jordy, look what you got here.
-What?
Look at this. $26,000 for one
fucking dinner!
Okay. No, no. This could be
explained.
Dad, we had clients. The Pfizer
clients.
Right. The porterhouse from
Argentina.
Expensive champagne and...
We had to buy champagne.
And you ordered all the fucking
sides.
-Tell him about the sides.
-I ordered sides, so...
Sides? $26,000 worth of sides?
What are these sides? They cure
cancer?
The sides did cure cancer.
That's the problem.
That's why they were expensive.
-Shut the fuck up.
-I'm serious.
-Stop.
-And EJ Entertainment?
What the fuck is EJ
Entertainment?
(ALL LAUGHING)
Well, that's...
DONNIE: Yeah, Jordy,
what's EJ Entertainment?
How do I describe this?
Jord, what is that?
It's a fucking prostitution
ring, Jordy!
I know.
-That's what it is!
-That is what it is.
Isn't that the perfect
description for it?
That is what it is.
But none of these were charged
to me.
This is all of them.
-Oh, that was all us?
-It wasn't me though.
Fucking explain this shit to
him!
These are all of your
fucking charges right here!
The IRS, they allow for T&A.
It's fine.
MAX: T&E!
T&E!
Yeah. I said T&E.
-No, no. You said T&A.
-No, I didn't.
Yeah, you did.
When did I say that?
You said T&A. It's T&E.
I know you're upset about the
dinner,
and that makes sense because we
did
spend too much money. But I said
T&E.
Don't tell me what you said.
I heard what you said.
-Dad. He said T&A.
-He did?
Absolutely, no question.
I'm trying to...
I'm getting this close!
-Dad, relax.
-I'm getting this close.
That's what I'm saying.
I want you to open up more, Max.
He's gonna fucking kill you.
Why do you hold it in? Why do
you...
Max, why do you hold it in?
That's it. Get the fuck out of
here!
No, no, no!
Asshole, get out of here.
What kind of hooker takes credit
cards?
A rich one.
JORDAN: At Stratton,
there were three kinds of
hookers.
The Blue Chips, top of
the line, model material.
They cost between $300 and $500
and you had to wear
a condom unless you gave them a
hefty tip,
which, of course, I always did.
Then came the NASDAQs,
who were pretty, not great.
They cost between 200 and 300
bucks.
Finally, there were the Pink
Sheets. Skanks.
They cost about 100 or less.
If you didn't wear a condom,
you'd have to get a penicillin
shot
the next day and pray your dick
didn't fall off.
Not that we didn't fuck them,
too.
Believe me, we did.
Ow! It's that slipped disk thing
again.
I know what it is. You know, too
much...
...with EJ Entertainment.
Pops.
How are things at home?
Well, not the best.
She just doesn't... You know
what I'm saying?
It's like the smell...
There's a smell, there's an
attraction thing.
After a while it kind of fades
away a little bit.
Yeah, well. It's supposed to
fade away.
-Supposed to?
-That's marriage. You know...
Your mother and I, we've been
married a long, long time.
What do you think? We're...
We're jumping into bed every two
minutes?
-It doesn't work that way.
-I love her to death.
I want to stay married, Dad,
but...
It's crazy out there.
Some of these girls... You
should see them.
Oh, my God!
They're fucking...
The things they're doing now,
Pops.
I mean... I mean, it's on a
whole other level.
-Really?
-And they're all shaved, too.
-Get out of here!
-All shaven.
-Are you kidding me?
-Yeah.
-Bald as a china doll.
-No bush?
-No bush.
-Oh, my God!
All of a sudden, one week,
nobody
had anything down there anymore.
It's a new world.
They're bald from the eyebrows
down.
Wow.
Nothing. Not a stitch. It's like
lasers.
Wow. A new world.
I was born too... Too early.
I've never been a fan
of the bush, to be honest.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I don't mind it.
Dad.
I don't want you stressing out
about any of this.
How can I not get stressed out?
Look at the knuckleheads
you got working for you.
I know they're knuckleheads
but I need them to want
to live like me, you get it?
To live like me.
Jordy.
One of these days,
the chickens are gonna come home
to roost.
You're looking at me like I'm
crazy.
(SCOFFS) Crazy? This is obscene.
JORDAN: It was obscene.
In the normal world.
But who the fuck wanted to live
there?
(CROWD CHEERING)
JORDAN: Go party your fucking
cocks off!
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
JORDAN: We are about to
become fucking legends
on Wall Street!
We got plans up here
that's gonna take this company
into the fucking stratosphere!
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: (CHANTING) Wolfie! Wolfie!
Fuck Merrill Lynch. Fuck them.
Why should they be taking all
our
fucking money all the fucking
time?
This way we become the
underwriters.
It was our next big move.
Finding companies to take
public. IPOs.
It was the only way these Wall
Street pricks
would ever stop thinking of us
as
some shitkicker bucket shop.
We got Arncliffe International.
JORDAN: See, we were a little
different.
We liked to get as fucked up as
possible during our business
powwows
in order to stimulate our
free-flowing ideas,
which is why we were
popping these ludes like they
were M&M's.
(SLURRING) Steve Madden.
We own the fucking companies...
-(GLASS SHATTERS)
-We own the companies...
Don't know what a lude is? I'll
tell you.
Oh, wait. Wait, wait, wait,
wait.
Looks like those ludes are
working
their magic on Donnie right now.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
JORDAN: The Quaalude,
or lude, as it is commonly
referred to,
was first synthesized in 1951
by an Indian doctor, that's
dots, not feathers,
as a sedative,
and was prescribed to
stressed-out
housewives with sleep disorders.
But pretty soon someone figured
out
that if you
resisted the urge to sleep for
just 15 minutes,
you got a pretty kick-ass high
from it.
Didn't take long for people
to start abusing ludes, of
course.
And in 1982,
the U.S. government Schedule 1'd
them.
Along with the rest of the
world.
Which meant there was
only a finite amount of these
things left.
No shit, you can't even buy 'em
anymore.
You people are all shit out of
luck.
What are you saying? What is it?
Steve Madden.
-(ALL LAUGHING)
-Steve Madden.
Steve.
JORDAN: You remember those ads?
Those giant-headed girls with
the bug eyes
wearing those big clunky shoes?
My friend from school, Steve
Madden.
His friend from school, Steve
Steve Madden was
the name in women's shoes at the
moment.
And all of Wall Street
was begging to take his company
public.
Go ahead, go ahead, what is it?
Except, guess who grew up with
him?
-Women's shoes.
My very own Vice President.
-Women's shoes!
-(ALL LAUGHING)
Diamond Donnie Azoff.
-Steve Madden.
-Steve.
Steve.
Hey, JB, JB, JB, JB.
You gotta come check this
fucking chick out.
Look at this. Look.
NICKY: I would fuck that girl
if she was my sister.
I would let that girl give me
fucking AIDS.
ROBBIE: You want to see
the Wolf handle this?
She's hot.
Cristy.
Jordan, this is my friend Naomi.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Naomi.
Naomi, nice to meet you.
You got an awesome place here.
I've don't think
I've ever been in a house this
big before.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
Beautiful beach out there.
Blair Hollingsworth.
Hi, Blair. Nice to meet you.
-Your name's Blair, right?
-Yeah.
You like to Jet Ski?
NAOMI: I've never done it
before.
-JORDAN: You've never Jet Ski'd
in your life?
-No, I've never Jet Ski'd.
You've never been on a Jet Ski?
How many times are you gonna ask
her?
She's never been on a Jet Ski.
I don't know.
Might ask her a couple more
times.
NAOMI: Okay. Sure.
(GIGGLING)
Hi. I'm Hildy. Nice to meet you.
-Hi.
-Jordan, Teresa needs your help.
Yeah, I'll be out in a couple of
minutes.
Just tell her I'll be out in a
couple of minutes.
Why don't you tell your wife
that?
I might do that, but I'm having
-a conversation right now.
-HILDY: What am I, your
secretary?
You know what, I think we should
get going.
Wait, wait. Where you guys
going?
We gotta go.
We got two other parties to go
to.
-We can stay for a drink.
-Yeah, stay for a drink.
No. We got two
other parties we're supposed to
get to.
NAOMI: But we can stay for a
drink...
She's
perfect.
-You like champagne?
-I do.
DONNIE: She's perfect.
Donnie, what the fuck are you
doing?
-You piece of...
-ALL: Oh!
(ALL LAUGHING)
You're gonna have to excuse my
friend.
He gets...
Get the fuck out!
Jordan, you gotta fuck her, bro.
She's so hot!
Yeah, Donnie!
NICKY: Let him fucking finish,
Hildy.
That's fucking rude.
Have some fucking manners.
JORDAN: So, Bay Ridge,
that's near Staten Island,
right?
Brooklyn, across the Verrazano
Bridge.
Saturday Night Fever territory.
That's right. Guinea Gulch.
We call the Verrazano Bridge
the Guinea Gangplank.
Right.
So I presume you're Italian?
On my dad's side.
I'm also Dutch, German, English.
I'm a mutt.
Yeah. You're a mutt.
Yeah, I still have family
over there though, in London.
My Aunt Emma. She's the best.
Very British, you know. She's a
classy lady.
That explains it then.
Explains what?
It explains you.
I mean, you're a duchess, right?
The Duchess of Bay Ridge.
Excuse me.
Could I get a straw, please?
Thank you.
So I was a little
surprised you asked Cristy for
my number.
Why is that?
Aren't you married?
Well... Yeah, but what?
Married people can't have
friends?
We're gonna be friends?
Yeah. You don't want to be my
friend?
We're not gonna be friends.
NAOMI: And at night I work on my
designs.
I have an entire line of
lingerie.
You know, camisoles, bustiers,
panties.
JORDAN: She designs women's
panties, too?
Oh, my God!
Come on, Jordan,
think of a way to get up to her
apartment.
You wanna come up
for some tea or something?
Tea? Yeah.
-Like hot tea?
-Yeah.
Oh, yeah. That sounds nice.
Yeah.
Tea. Fuck, yeah, I wanted to
come up for tea.
Like Darjeeling or rose hip,
something nice like that?
NAOMI: Sure.
This is Rocky.
Oh, who's this? Say hi, Rocky.
-Hi, sweetheart.
-(BARKS)
Okay.
Why don't you light
a fire or something and I'll be
right out.
-Yeah. Fire, here?
-Sure.
I like your painting here.
It's...
God, help me. How do I fuck this
girl?
(CLATTERING)
You all right?
Yeah, yeah. Just trying to light
the fire here.
(BEEPER RINGING)
That's it. That's it, you're
leaving.
Don't get involved. Go home to
your wife.
(DOOR OPENING)
As you can probably guess,
I fucked her goddamn brains
out...
JORDAN: (GRUNTING) Jesus Lord!
(NAOMI MOANING)
For 11 seconds.
(JORDAN GROANS)
NAOMI: Did you just come?
JORDAN: Oh, yeah, I just came.
Did you? Did you come?
-No.
-No?
Okay.
I'm still hard so just give me a
sec.
Sure.
Come on, baby, come on.
(BARKING)
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
(ROCKY BARKING)
Oh, God!
NAOMI: Fuck off, Rocky! Bad dog.
You have a biscuit or something
like that?
It's okay.
-Just keep going.
-Rocky, go play.
Go play, Rocky. Go, go, go, go.
(WHISTLES)
(ROCKY BARKING)
You're crazy.
JORDAN: I couldn't get enough.
I mean, her pussy was like
heroin to me.
And it wasn't just about the
sex, either.
Naomi and I got along. I mean,
we...
We had similar interests and
shit.
(NAOMI GIGGLING)
Ooh! Choo-choo train.
Yeah.
(IMITATES TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
I think I can. I think I can.
(SNORTING)
(LAUGHS)
Yeah, yeah. Let's toke it all on
there, huh?
Whoo!
Oh, shit!
You!
Get out of the fucking car!
-(GRUNTING)
-JORDAN: Jesus Christ.
Son of a bitch! Oh, fuck!
Relax, sweetheart. Relax.
-Son of a fucking bitch!
-Okay, okay... Geez!
Okay, babe, stop! Ow!
Please.
(GRUNTS) Bitch!
-What are you doing...
-That whore from the party?
(GROANS) Jesus Christ!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I thought you were at the
fucking beach!
I didn't know you were here!
That's where you've fucking
been?
With that fucking whore from the
party?
I thought you were at the beach
house.
How could you do this to me?
(SOBBING)
Sweetie, come on...
Who the fuck are you, Jordan?
You're like a completely
different fucking person!
I made a mistake.
I don't know what to tell you,
babe. I...
I'm sorry.
Is that who... Is that what you
want?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Do you love her?
Answer me.
(SOBBING)
JORDAN: I felt horrible.
Three days later, I filed for a
divorce
and moved Naomi into the
apartment.
Say what you will,
but the Duchess did have style.
She brought in a decorator,
feng shui'd the whole place.
She even hired a gay butler.
This guy was smart,
sophisticated, professional.
Really, really great.
Is that jasmine?
Yes, sir. I tried to stump you
this evening.
Very good.
Very good. Great nose.
JORDAN: Except for that one
time.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS)
Oh, my God!
Oh, hey.
Is it Wednesday already?
-Uh...
-MAN: Oh, don't stop.
What the fuck!
That is fucked up!
He must have thought we were
still
at the Hamptons this weekend,
you know.
Where were they doing it,
sweetheart?
In the bedroom?
They were everywhere.
There were two guys over there
on the table.
There were more over here.
There were four right here.
Oh! Are you fucking serious?
Right there?
Why didn't you tell me?
Oh, baby, it gets worse.
(SNIFFLES)
After they left, I checked the
apartment.
Right. What?
What is it, babe? What?
JORDAN: Where's my money?
I don't know where your money...
Where is my fucking money? Where
is it?
I don't know where your money
is, Mr. Belfort.
I didn't do anything.
If you don't get...
He's lying through his fucking
teeth.
Let's start from the beginning.
Let's start from the beginning,
all right?
You invited some friends over,
right?
One thing led to another.
Things got out of hand.
We understand that, we do.
(CHUCKLES)
We do blow all the time.
We're fucking degenerates
ourselves.
Look at us, right?
But money was stolen from my
apartment.
Right from my sock drawer. All
right?
Like I said, I don't know where
your money is.
Just start from the beginning.
Who came over?
It was just a normal day.
I knew you were coming home the
next day.
So everything would be fine.
It'd be cleaned up.
I got a little high at
breakfast.
So I got a little happy. I had
some eggs,
I had a little bit of ice cream.
And then I said,
"Who do I know that likes ice
cream?"
It's my friend, Rudy. So I
called Rudy.
DONNIE: Who's Rudy?
Yeah, who's Rudy?
You know who Rudy is. Come on.
Me? I don't...
-You know...
-Who the fuck is Rudy?
I don't know anyone named Rudy.
Last month. The Lollipop Club.
You know who Rudy was.
Dancing...
-You know who Rudy is?
-(STAMMERING)
I don't fucking know any...
What do you mean?
So he went to The Lollipop Club?
NICHOLAS: Oh, he was
at The Lollipop Club for sure.
On the stage, grinding with
everybody.
I got fucked up. I like to
dance.
I don't know. Maybe I met him,
maybe I didn't.
I meet a lot of fucking people.
-What are you saying?
-$50,000 was stolen
from my fucking sock drawer!
All my girlfriend's jewelry is
gone.
-Where the fuck is it?
-...Rudy. What the fuck?
Did your fucking
little faggot friend Rudy take
my shit?
Did he? Answer me!
Okay. Now I get it. Now I get
why I'm...
-This is a gay thing.
-JORDAN: Oh!
-See, all of you...
-(CHUCKLING)
You think this is 'cause you're
a fag?
My cousin's a fucking faggot.
And I go on vacation
with him and his boyfriend. I
love fags.
JORDAN: You were in charge,
right?
I will not be stolen from. You
get that?
I fucking like gay people. I
don't like you.
He should've hired a fucking
Mexican
like I have in my fucking house.
(GROANING)
Shit! What the fuck...
TOBY: Talk, you fuck, talk!
CHESTER: I'm gonna drop you, you
faggot!
-TOBY: Where is it?
-(NICHOLAS SCREAMING)
JORDAN: Chester and Toby,
they went all yakuza on
Nicholas.
You know, they got crazy.
I don't know!
JORDAN: I had to call the cops
just to keep
them from killing the poor guy.
I gave them each 1,000 bucks
and told them what Nicholas had
done.
Then they kicked his ass.
Thanks again, Officer.
It's not like I cared about
the 50 grand anyway.
I was making that much almost
every day
through one rathole or another.
Now a rathole is a friend, like
Brad here,
who held stock in his name for
me.
Who are you supposed to be, huh?
Jack Nickle-Jew?
JORDAN: I'd drive the price up
then he'd sell
and kick most of the profits
back to...
You guessed it, me.
All cash. None of it's on the
books.
A big no-no, of course, in the
eyes of the law.
Enter our new securities
attorney,
Manny Riskin.
700 bucks an hour to be the
voice of doom.
Listen to me. You piss up the
SEC's leg,
you end up with your tits in a
ringer.
Do not worry about it.
I have the SEC under control.
What the fuck are these
imbeciles doing?
Hey! Hey!
-What are you doing? Hey!
-(WHOOPING)
We got the SEC in here.
JORDAN: The Securities
and Exchange Commission
sent two lawyers down to review
our files.
So I set them up in our
conference room
and I had it bugged
and the air conditioning turned
up so high
that it felt like Antarctica in
there.
Is it always this cold in here?
I don't know.
JORDAN: Then, while they were
looking
for a smoking gun in that
room...
Arncliffe International is on
fire.
...I was gonna fire off a
bazooka in here,
offering up our latest IPO.
An IPO is an initial public
offering.
It's the first time a stock is
offered
for sale to the general
population.
Now, as the firm taking the
company public,
we set the initial sales price
then sold those shares
right back to our friends.
The...
Look. (CHUCKLES)
I know you're not following
what I'm saying anyway, right?
That's okay. That doesn't
matter.
The real question is this.
(WHISPERS) "Was all this legal?"
Absolutely fucking not.
But we were making more money
than we knew what to do with.
And what do you do when you're
making
more money than you know what to
do with?
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, my God!
Will you marry me?
Oh, my God.
Is that a yes?
(CHUCKLES)
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure. Yeah, I'm sure.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
JORDAN: I held my bachelor party
at the Mirage in Las Vegas.
The flight there alone was a
bacchanal.
One last blowout
for the gods before I settled
down for good.
A hundred Strattonites,
50 hookers,
plus 50 more waiting once we
landed.
Oh, and the drugs.
I mean, I tell you, our plane
was like a pharmacy with wings.
(BEEPING)
(ELECTRIC BLUES MUSIC PLAYING)
All told, the weekend
cost me two million bucks,
including the cost
of refurbishing the entire 28th
floor.
WOMAN: ...kiss the bride.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
JORDAN: Ah! But the wedding
was something out of a fairy
tale.
With Naomi, my Duchess,
me, her handsome Duke,
and The Bahamas Ocean Club, our
castle.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Of course,
after the bachelor party, me,
the Duke,
needed a few penicillin shots so
he could
safely consummate the marriage.
(SINGING)
Hey! Barry Kleinman, filming the
wedding.
A few words for your son?
Jordan. Remember what I told
you.
It involves your penis and her
vagina.
And you know, you know
what you can do, Jordy.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(BLUES MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, my God!
Aunt Emma?
I can't believe you came!
Jordan! Jordan! Look who came!
It's Aunt Emma.
Aunt Emma.
Oh, Jordan, dear, how lovely.
Hey, how you doing?
It's a pleasure to finally meet
you in person.
Into the donuts, I see.
Oh, I... I...
Well...
I lived through the '60s, my
dear.
Enjoy the day.
She surprised me. I didn't even
know.
(LAUGHING)
JORDAN: Just one more step. Are
you ready?
-NAOMI: Where are we going?
-Keep your eyes closed.
One, two, three!
What is this?
JORDAN: (CHUCKLING)
It's your wedding present.
-What?
-It's your wedding present,
sweetheart.
What?
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
A fucking yacht?
ROBIN LEACH: For millionaires
whose ships have come in,
pricey pleasure boats
are for the most fun afloat.
It's no coincidence that
its 150 feet of green hull
is the color of cash. Anchors
aweigh!
Oh, my God! Baby!
-I think you like it?
-You're crazy.
-You like it?
-Yes!
JORDAN: For three weeks,
we sailed the Naomi through the
Caribbean,
eventually taking her home to
Long Island,
where we bought a house.
Seven acres on
the Gold Coast of Long Island.
The most expensive real estate
in the world.
With maids, cooks, landscapers,
you name it.
We even had two guards
who worked in shifts.
Both named Rocco.
It was heaven on earth.
NAOMI: Wake up, you piece of
shit!
-Ow!
-Who's Venice?
-Huh?
-Who?
Who? Who?
"Who?" What are you, a fucking
owl?
-Who is she?
-(STUTTERING)
Some little hooker
you were fucking last night?
What the fuck are you talking
about? No.
No way, baby, no!
You were calling her name in
your sleep!
Are you out of your fucking
mind? I don't...
I don't even know who Venice is.
What the fuck does that even
mean? Venice.
That's the stupidest shit
I've ever heard in my fucking
life!
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
JORDAN: (SLURRING) Venice...
Venice, baby, where are you?
Venice!
Where'd you go?
(GROANING)
Oh, baby. Oh, you're gonna play
rough, huh?
-Oh, Jesus Christ!
-You like that?
(GROANING)
I like it. I like it. Ow!
Wolfie, Wolfie, Wolfie, Wolfie.
Wolfie?
Yeah, it's my safe word, baby.
It's my safe word.
I don't give a fuck about your
safe word!
(SCREAMS) Oh! Come on!
Shut the fuck up!
-Ahh!
-Shut up, you little bitch!
You're a fucking dirty little
birdy! Owie!
That's right.
That's right! I forgot.
(CHUCKLING) I forgot, baby.
Donnie and I were investing in a
condominium complex in Venice.
That's why all this confusion.
Oh, you're investing in Italy?
Not Italy. California.
-Oh, California?
-Yeah.
You're a lying piece of shit!
Duchess, baby, come on.
Don't you fucking "Duchess" me.
-Don't you "Duchess" me!
-(APOLOGIZING)
Do you really think
that I don't know what you're up
to?
-You're a father now, Jordan.
-Yeah.
-You're a father now.
-I know...
And you're still acting like an
infant!
(SCREAMS)
God damn it!
Baby, you know, you got real
anger issues.
Who is the one who flew in here
at 3:00 in the morning
on their stupid helicopter
and woke up Skylar? That was
you!
Oh, Skylar! Oh, fucking
bullshit!
-(ALARMS BLARING)
-(BABY CRYING)
Does it even matter
to you that I just had that
driving range
sodded with Bermuda grass,
Jordan,
-and now you fucking wrecked it!
-Oh, my God... Bermuda grass.
No, you didn't research the
whole thing
and deal with the fucking golf
course people!
Oh, my God,
you had to deal
with the golf course people,
too!
What a Greek tragedy, honey! Oh,
my God!
You probably had to pay them
in cash with your hands!
What a fucking burden.
And actually do some work
besides swiping
my fucking credit card all day,
huh?
Because I can't keep track
of your professions, honey.
'Cause last month
you were a wine connoisseur.
Now you're an aspiring landscape
architect!
-Let me get that right... No!
-Fuck you!
Don't fucking dare throw that
fucking water at me. Don't you
fucking dare.
All right, honey?
Now will you just...
We could talk this out, all
right?
We just use our words. You know?
Communicate.
Okay?
Come on, sweetheart.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
Stop flexing your muscles,
Jordan.
You look like a fucking
imbecile.
Babe, come on.
You should feel happy you got a
husband
who's in such great shape like
this, huh?
Come here.
Come on, give me a kiss.
You look so beautiful right now.
-Come on.
-Kiss you?
-You look so beautiful...
Yeah, give me one...
Fuck you!
Ah, yes, my morning ritual.
First I'd get up and fight with
Naomi
about whatever it is I did the
night before.
Next was a steam so I could
sweat out
the drugs still in my system.
Then I'd assess the damage.
Drown out my eyeballs.
Take my "back pills" to get the
day started,
then seek to make up with Naomi.
Good morning, Daddy.
Where's my kiss?
Whee!
Hey, sweetheart.
Does Daddy get
a kiss from both of his little
girls, huh?
Oh, no.
No, Daddy doesn't even get to
touch Mommy
for a very, very,
very long time.
Daddy's really sorry
about what he said in the other
room.
He didn't mean any of it.
Daddy shouldn't waste his time.
And from now on,
it's gonna be nothing but short,
short skirts around the house.
And you know something else,
Daddy?
Mommy is just so sick
and tired of wearing panties.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
In fact,
she's decided to throw them
all away.
(SIGHING)
So take a good look, Daddy.
You're gonna be seeing
an awful lot of this around the
house.
Oh, baby...
Yeah, Mommy.
-Yeah...
-But no touching.
Oh, gosh.
What's wrong, Daddy?
Baby.
God! (SOBBING)
Look at this shit.
Okay. Mommy likes to play games
with Daddy.
Mommy, have you ever noticed
anything odd about Mr...
Mr. Fuzzy Bear over there?
His eyes seem
to be a little bit odd, don't
they?
Yeah, there's something
a little bit different about his
eyes.
(GASPS) Yes! I think it's true.
Say "Hi," Mommy.
Say "Hi" to Rocco and Rocco.
-Say "Hi." Hi, fellas.
-(CHUCKLES)
See that, huh?
JORDAN: Of all the fucking days,
she chooses today to give me
blue balls!
I mean, today was
the biggest day in Stratton's
history,
and I needed to be thinking
straight.
Hey, Jordan!
-Welcome.
-Steve here yet?
JORDAN: This was the day
that we launched the Steve
Madden IPO.
DONNIE: Troops are all here,
everyone's all rallied, excited.
JORDAN: Everything had to run
tight.
It had to be perfect.
What the fuck is that kid doing?
What's he doing?
The biggest IPO in this firm's
history.
What the fuck is he doing?
JANET: Is he... Is he wearing a
bow tie?
Hi.
How're you doing?
Good.
You cleaning the fish bowl?
I just... I had a minute and...
You had a minute.
And today you needed
to clean the fish bowl? Today?
I had finished my paperwork
and I had a couple of minutes.
Okay. Nice to meet you.
On new issue day?
On cocksucking,
motherfucking new issue day?
This is what you do?
Hey, everybody, listen up!
This is what happens when you
fuck
with your pets on new issue day!
(ALL GROANING)
Take your little bow tie, get
your shit,
and get the fuck out of my
office!
You understand?
Get the fuck out!
(ALL JEERING)
Everybody on point!
We are here to make money.
Everybody on point.
JORDAN: A real wolf pit,
which is exactly how I liked it.
Jordan, look what I caught in
the lobby.
I caught a genius.
JORDAN: Enter Steve Madden.
The great American cobbler.
Red-hot ladies footwear
impresario.
And thanks to Donnie,
we were taking his company
public.
Stratton Oakmont
was crawling out of the
primordial ooze.
Pond scum no more.
That's why they gotta see your
face.
You get them fired up so they
push
the shit out of this stock.
Okay?
And not only that,
Donnie and I secretly owned
85% of Steve Madden Shoes,
which legally speaking was a big
no-no,
but we'd get filthy fucking rich
if our troops got behind it.
Our job was to get them worked
up.
-But not too worked up.
-Shh.
-Hello. If, uh...
-(WHISTLES)
For those of you who don't know
me...
My name's Steve Madden.
-Yeah, we know who you are.
-(LAUGHTER)
Your name is on the box.
Get the shoes. Show them the
shoes.
-Show them the shoes.
-Okay. Yeah.
Anyway, you know, this shoe is
pretty cool.
This is the Mary Lou, which is
really
the shoe that put me on the map.
Without it, I wouldn't be here.
It's a fat girls' shoe!
Believe it or not... Believe it
or not though,
the Mary Lou is actually the
same
as the Mary Jane, but it's black
leather.
(JEERING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Fight back! Come on!
Where you at? Where you at?
All right!
Let's give it up
for Steve Madden and his awesome
Mary Lou!
Hold that up. Hold that up.
Hold that up proud!
Give him a round of applause!
You guys got that out of your
systems, huh?
You having a good afternoon or
what?
I wanna take a moment
and tell you why Steve here is
so
absolutely off the fucking wall.
It's because this man is a
creative genius.
This ability, this gift that
Steve has,
it goes beyond
just spotting the hottest shoe
trends.
Steve's power is that he creates
You understand?
Artists like Steve
come along once every decade.
I'm talking Giorgio Armani,
Gianni Versace, Coco Chanel,
Yves Saint Laurent.
Steve, come over here for a
second.
I don't think you all realize
that Steve Madden
is the hottest person
in the women's shoe industry,
with orders going through the
roof
at every department store
in North America right now.
We have him here in our office!
We should thank
our fucking lucky stars this man
is here!
We should be on our hands
and knees right now,
getting ready to suck this guy
off!
Like this! Okay?
(LAUGHTER)
I wanna suck you off, Steve!
Everyone's gonna suck you off!
This is our golden ticket
to the fucking chocolate factory
right here!
-(CHEERING)
-And I wanna meet
Willy fucking Wonka, okay?
I wanna be with the fucking
Oompa Loompas like this!
All right, get off this fucking
stage!
Get out of here.
All right, I want all of you
to focus for a second.
See those little black boxes?
They're called telephones.
I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret about these
telephones.
They're not gonna dial
themselves. Okay?
Without you, they're just
worthless hunks of plastic.
Like a loaded M16 without
a trained Marine to pull the
trigger.
And in the case of the
telephone,
it's up to each and every one of
you,
my highly-trained Strattonites.
My killers!
My killers, who will not take no
for an answer!
My fucking warriors,
who will not hang up the phone
until their client either buys
or fucking dies!
(ALL CHEERING)
Let me tell you something.
There is no nobility in poverty.
I have been a rich man
and I have been a poor man.
And I choose rich every fucking
time.
(CHEERING)
Because at least as a rich man,
when I have to face my problems,
I show up in the back of a limo,
wearing a $2,000 suit
and a $40,000 gold fucking
watch!
(YELLING)
Duke it out! Hit him!
Get the fuck off me!
And if anyone here
thinks I'm superficial or
materialistic,
go get a job at fucking
McDonald's,
'cause that's where you fucking
belong!
But before you depart
this room full of winners,
I want you to take a good look
at the person next to you. Go
on.
Because sometime in
the not-so-distant future,
you're gonna be pulling up to a
red light
in your beat-up old fucking
Pinto,
and that person's gonna be
pulling up right alongside you
in their brand new Porsche
with their beautiful wife by
their side,
who's got big voluptuous tits.
(ALL LAUGH)
And who're you gonna be sitting
next to?
Some disgusting wildebeest
with three days of
razor-stubble,
in a sleeveless muumuu,
crammed in next to you
in a carload full of groceries
from the fucking Price Club!
That's who you're gonna be
sitting next to!
So you listen to me and you
listen well.
Are you behind on your credit
card bills?
Good! Pick up the phone and
start dialing!
Is your landlord ready to evict
you? Good!
Pick up the phone and start
dialing!
Does your girlfriend
think you're a fucking worthless
loser?
Good! Pick up the phone and
start dialing!
I want you to deal
with your problems by becoming
rich!
(ALL CHEERING)
All you have to do today is pick
up that phone
and speak the words that I have
taught you.
And I will make you richer
than the most powerful CEO
in the United States of fucking
America!
-Yeah!
-(CHEERING)
Fuck, yeah!
I want you to go out there
and I want you to ram
Steve Madden stock
down your clients' throats
until they fucking choke on it!
Till they choke on it and they
buy
100,000 shares! That's what I
want.
Yeah! Fuck, yeah.
You be ferocious!
-You be relentless!
-ALL: Yeah!
You be telephone fucking
terrorists!
Now let's knock
this motherfucker out of the
park!
-(CHEERING LOUDLY)
-Oh!
(PEPPY SONG PLAYING)
JORDAN: At 1:00 p.m.,
we opened the stock for sale at
$4.50 a share.
By 1:03, it was over $18.
Even the big Wall Street firms
were buying.
Of the two million shares
offered for sale,
a million belonged to me,
held in phony accounts by my
ratholes.
Now once the price hit the high
teens...
(CHUCKLES) You know what?
Who gives a shit?
As always, the point is this.
$22 million in three fucking
hours!
Can you believe this shit?
I fucking love this, baby!
It's amazing!
JANET: Jordan!
Barry Kleinman's on the phone
-from Future Video.
-Who?
I don't know. He shot at your
wedding.
He says it's urgent.
Urgent? Who the fuck is Barry
Kleinman?
Oh, my God, you wanna marry me?
You're in love with me?
Yeah. Go fuck your cousin!
Hey, Barry, what's up?
Listen, I got this subpoena.
Subpoena? What the fuck
are you talking about?
Yeah, the FBI, they want
a copy of your wedding video.
JORDAN: The fucking FBI?
-You fucking kidding me?
-BO: Listen to me.
His name is Denham.
He's an agent with the New York
office.
JORDAN: What's his problem?
BO: He's a Boy Scout.
He thinks you're fucking Gordon
Gekko.
JORDAN: What does he want
with my wedding video?
It's like an invasion of my
privacy.
You know what I'm saying?
It's like... It's intrusive, you
know.
He's got pictures of your
whole inner fucking circle.
Pictures, names of the people.
You know what he's trying to do?
Exactly what he's doing. Look at
yourself.
He's trying to rattle you,
he's trying to rattle your old
lady,
so she nags you until
you become a fucking witness.
He wants me to rat on myself?
He wants me to give information
about my...
Listen. The good fucking news
is,
you know I know everybody
downtown,
I call up the Justice
Department, the DEA,
nobody even knows
you fucking exist, so calm down!
They don't know I exist?
-No.
-That's good.
But you...
You know who he is, right?
-Yeah.
-So, if I just wanted to get
some more information,
just find out what he knows,
(WHISPERING) you could
go to his house, right?
Tap his phones a little bit, bug
him.
You could get some
information...
You don't fuck with these guys
like that.
You don't fuck with them like
that.
What are you, nuts or something?
This is what you fucking do.
What do I pay you for?
I have a fucking P.I. license,
you know?
I make a living at this.
I'm not a cop anymore.
They'll take my fucking license
away
from me, all right?
Okay.
Okay, if I can't do that, can I
just...
Can I give the guy a call?
-Why? Is that...
-Jordan. Jordan.
Do me a favor?
The only one
who calls this guy is your
fucking lawyer.
I can't call him, right?
-It's against the rules?
-I told you,
whatever the fuck you say to
him,
he's gonna use against you.
Don't you understand?
He's smart, you're dumb.
Fucking bullshit.
Are we fucking talking tonight,
or are you gonna get schwacked?
The last time you took these
fucking pills,
you put your head in the fucking
macaroni.
I had to pick it up.
All right.
Okay, I won't call him.
Hey, fellas! Come on board.
The plank's right around there.
Welcome!
Ooh! What a nice day.
Hey.
Welcome aboard.
Jordan. Welcome aboard the
Naomi.
Pleasure to meet you.
Agent Denham. This is Agent
Hughes.
Hi, how are you?
Let me introduce you.
This is Nicole, Heidi. Come on.
Don't be shy.
What are you guys all shy for?
Don't be scared.
These are friends of Stratton.
-It's a pleasure.
-Hello.
Um...
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Your message said
that you wanted to speak
privately.
Right. I do want to speak
Give us a minute, huh, ladies?
Let me know if I can get you
anything.
We'd be happy to help.
You guys hungry?
Want something to eat?
Got some pasta, shrimp, lobster.
I got whiskey. Any kind of booze
you want.
You know what? The Bureau
doesn't allow us
to drink while we're at sea.
Duh! Of course.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Ever been on one of these
before?
A boat?
I learned how to sail when I was
six.
No shit. Is that right? Really?
On one like this, though?
I had the whole front extended
in
order to fit the chopper up
there.
See that?
Anyway, this is for you.
It's a complete list of every
person
that was at my wedding.
I understand you wanted
the whole wedding video.
Figured this would help
expedite the whole process,
right?
-There you go.
-Look,
my point is that
I know you're investigating
Stratton.
But for the life of me, I can't
figure out why.
I know we're a little
unorthodox,
we're a little loud in the way
we do things.
But you gotta understand,
we're the new guys on the block,
you know,
we're trying to make a name for
ourselves.
But I want you to understand,
we don't do anything illegal.
Whatsoever.
I mean, you could talk to the
SEC.
They were at my office
15 times over the last six
months.
I mean, I got... I got nothing
to hide.
Well, you know the SEC
is a civil regulatory agency.
We pursue criminal activities.
Exactly! You go after real
criminals,
which makes me wonder
what the hell you're
investigating me for?
-(BOTH CHUCKLING)
-I mean, honestly...
What is it that you think that
we did or do?
I don't get it.
Well, I...
Look, Jordan, I can't discuss
an ongoing investigation.
No, I get that. No, I
understand.
With that said...
This case got dumped on my
desk...
-Did it?
-You know, by a higher-up
who needs to make a show of
looking
into the new company on the
block,
-with all the press and
everything.
-New loud guys.
And then I end up being the
schmuck
who does the looking. Exactly.
It's just, you know... It
bothers me.
We're the new guy. We're the one
that's banging on Wall Street's
door.
I mean, you should...
You should see what's going
on at the bigger firms.
I mean, I know all the
information.
It's true! Goldman, Lehman
Brothers, Merrill...
Collateralized debt obligations?
This Internet stock bullshit?
I mean, it's a fucking travesty.
I could take you step-by-step
through what exactly is
occurring.
All you have to do is ask.
I'm available.
-That's exactly what I wanted to
hear.
-Mmm-hmm.
I don't see why a little sitdown
like this
can't be profitable for the both
of us.
It should. Right?
It should profit the both of us.
-It should.
-Look.
I'm gonna give you my personal
line.
Five days a week, you just call
me, feel free.
-I'll do that.
-Great.
Are you sure
you guys don't want something to
drink?
You're not hungry? Nothing?
-Nothing? No?
-Oh, no.
Let me ask you,
and if you don't wanna get too
personal,
-just tell me to shut up at any
time.
-Oh.
Did you try to get your
broker's license at one time?
Did I hear that right?
Were you trying to take a stab
at Wall Street?
-No? (CHUCKLES)
-Who you been talking to?
Who the fuck you been talking
to?
Well, you're investigating me.
-I hear things.
-(LAUGHING)
You know what I mean?
You ever think about what
would've happened
if you would have stayed the
course?
You know what?
When I'm riding home on the
subway
and my balls are fucking
sweating,
I'm wearing the same suit
three days in a row...
Yeah, you bet I do.
I've thought about it before.
Who wouldn't, right?
Right, who fucking wouldn't?
What do you get...
Another personal question,
no need to answer...
No, that's all right, Jordan.
What do you pull in? 50, 60K?
Something like that?
-A year? In the ballpark?
-Oh.
Well, I...
Let's put it this way.
You get a free handgun when you
sign up
-for the Bureau.
-(CHUCKLING)
No, but it fucking pisses me
off.
You know what I mean?
You think about the people
that built this country,
hardworking people like you.
Firefighters, teachers, FBI
agents.
End of the day, you guys
get fucking skinned alive
financially.
It fucking makes me angry.
Now the one thing
about Wall Street and this
market is,
for me, I feel
it's good to give back. You
know, there's...
There are situations where I can
make those situations better for
people.
You know?
You know what I mean.
Opportunity
is everything.
Exactly.
Take for example, I got this one
kid, right?
Went to school for environmental
science,
something like that.
He was bogged down by student
loans.
Turns out, his mother
needed triple bypass surgery.
-Jesus.
-Right. Horrible situation.
Sure.
But we got him into the market
at the right time and chose the
right stock.
We gave him the right guidance.
Boom! Overnight, changed his
entire life.
Got to put his mother
into the best hospital in New
York City.
It didn't work out for her,
granted,
she passed away, unfortunately.
But we gave him that
opportunity.
You know what I'm saying?
It's just about setting up the
right team,
and then overnight your life can
change.
What does... What does an
intern...
What does an intern make in a
deal like that?
Well, in that situation,
in that particular trade, and it
was one trade,
north of half a million dollars.
And I'd do that for anybody, you
know,
anybody that needs the proper
guidance.
Can you say that again,
just the way you said it?
Just the same way.
Oh.
I don't know what you're talking
about.
Oh, come on!
You know what I'm talking about.
I think what Jordan just did is
he...
-If I'm not mistaken...
-No.
...you just tried to bribe a
federal officer.
No, technically I didn't bribe
anybody.
No, no, that's not
the conversation I heard,
Jordan.
No, no, according to the U.S.
criminal code,
there needs to be an exact
dollar figure
-for the exchange of services.
-Oh!
That would not hold up in a
court of law.
Nah, it's not how I heard it.
No, no, no, that's the truth.
But I want to tell you this.
Yeah.
The same gentleman that told me
that you tried to get your
broker's license
also told me that you are a
straight arrow.
He ran a security check on me.
Well...
Yeah, when you sail
on a boat fit for a Bond
villain,
sometimes you need to play the
part. Right?
I think it's time you both
get the fuck off my boat.
-What do you say? Hmm?
-(CHUCKLING)
You know, Jordan, I'll tell you
something.
Most of the Wall Street
jackasses that I bust,
they're to the manor born.
-Is that right?
-Yeah.
Their fathers are douchebags,
just like their fathers before
them.
But you...
You, Jordan,
you got this way all on your
own.
Did I?
-Good for you, little man.
-Little man?
-(LAUGHING)
-Good for you.
Me, the little man?
And let me tell you something.
Let me tell you something else.
Honestly, I'm not bullshitting
here,
this is one of the nicest boats
-that I've ever been on, I gotta
tell you.
-I bet it is.
And you know what I was just
thinking, too?
The fucking hero
that I'm gonna be back at the
office
when the Bureau seizes this
fucking boat.
Because, I mean,
fuckety-fuck-fuck, Jordan,
-look at this thing!
-(BOTH LAUGHING LOUDLY)
It's beautiful!
And you got the beautiful girls
there.
It's wonderful.
All right, get the fuck off my
boat.
I'm sure we'll be seeing each
other
-real soon.
-I'm sure.
Good luck on that subway ride
home
to your miserable, ugly fucking
wives.
I'm gonna have Heidi
lick some caviar off my balls in
the meantime.
Hey, you guys want to
take some lobsters for your ride
home?
Fucking miserable pricks,
I know you can't afford them!
Fucking cheap fucks.
Fucking miserable pricks.
(WHISTLES)
Hey, fellas!
Look what I found in my pocket!
Look!
A year's salary right here.
You know what I call them? Fun
coupons!
See that!
They're fun coupons!
(SIGHS)
Switzerland? What the fuck is in
Switzerland?
JORDAN: Swiss fucking banks,
that's what.
It was ass-covering time.
I had to hide my money.
Enter Rugrat.
He knew this Swiss banker from
law school.
-That's for European pussy!
-JORDAN: But he was in Geneva.
And there was no way
I was gonna make that flight
sober.
So I knew if I took my drugs
right,
I could sleep through the entire
flight.
But I had to take them just
right.
At 4:00 p.m., I popped a few
more ludes,
which started kicking in by the
time I finished my sales
meeting.
My tingle phase.
By dinner, I popped a few more
on top of some cocktails and a
Valium or two.
My slur phase.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
By 8:30, I took a few more ludes
and pretty much lost all my
motor skills.
This was the drool phase.
And by 10:00, I didn't know
who or what the fuck I was.
The amnesia phase.
We boarded the plane just before
midnight.
Wow! Look at you!
-You're beautiful.
-Excuse me, sir.
His sleeping pills just kicked
in. He's all right.
May I see your boarding passes,
sir?
We have the boarding passes.
Jesus Christ, I wanna fuck her.
Hey! Fucking relax.
Oh, my God!
You got your hand on my fucking
cock!
I don't. Cut it out.
He's got his hand on my dick
again.
I'm just trying to buckle you
up.
You got your hand on his dick?
You gotta stop doing that in
public places.
Oh, my God. Take it off!
Take it off!
I heard there's a treasure map
under here.
Stop! I know, miss.
Excuse me, sir.
Please sit down.
-Watch it.
-Go back to your seat, please.
What are you upset about?
Please go back to your seat.
I will have to call the captain.
Please, sir, please, sir. Sit
down.
-Please sit down!
-NICKY: Ow!
-I'm going! Stop.
-Okay, sorry.
We apologize. We're gonna go to
sleep.
Question. I wanna ask you a
question.
Fasten your seat belt, sir.
We cannot take off if you
haven't fastened
-your seat belt.
-I'm really horny, too.
Sit down. Fasten it.
-DONNIE: Right. Okay, I'll sit
down...
-I will do it for you.
-What?
-I'll do it for you.
JORDAN: You gotta speak English.
We don't understand
this language you're speaking.
I will help him with his seat
belt.
-You gotta put it on right.
-Sit back. Sit back, sir.
-There you go.
-All right. I'll just lean
back...
(LAUGHING)
Bitte, Hilfe!
(BOTH MIMICKING STEWARDESS)
Jesus Christ!
Fuck!
Donnie...
Donnie, this isn't funny.
You gotta untie me, buddy.
I can't untie you.
The captain tied you up.
He almost fucking tasered you.
-Why?
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
He's got a fear of flying.
Ahh!
DONNIE: He's very nervous
on planes, I'm sorry,
it's not you, sweetheart,
don't beat yourself up.
Easy, easy. He's fine.
He's just a nervous flyer.
You were screaming at people.
Oh, fuck off.
You were on the floor rolling
around and shit.
Oh, Jesus.
You called the captain the
N-word.
I called the captain the N-word?
-Yeah, he was very upset.
-Really?
Luckily we're in first class.
Jesus.
Jesus Christ,
I think you have a fucking drug
problem.
Where are the ludes?
They're up my ass. Don't worry
about it.
-I got it.
-(SIGHS) Okay.
Thank God.
Jesus Christ, what are we gonna
do
when we get to Switzerland,
buddy?
This is bad.
Fucking things are against my
chest.
I can't breathe.
Come on,
do something to calm me down.
Please.
Okay, shut the fuck up. Shut the
fuck up.
-(WHIMPERING)
-Okay. Shh! Shh!
-That's good.
-(SING-SONG) Go to sleep.
Rub it harder, buddy.
You're all right.
We all love you. Shut the fuck
up!
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
Mr. Belfort, you're free to go.
Really?
Whoo!
-NICKY: Hey, Donnie.
-Yeah?
NICKY: When we get out there,
try not to act like yourself.
Okay? Let's make Geneva
an asshole-free Donnie zone, all
right?
DONNIE: What are you
fucking coming at me for?
Hey, listen.
The only reason you're sitting
in this limo
and not in a Swiss jail
is because of my friend. Okay?
-Hilfe!
-(ALL CHUCKLE)
NICKY: We're here. We're here.
Everyone calm down.
Jordan Belfort!
At last.
Nicholas has told me so much
about you.
Jordan, Jean Jacques Saurel.
Pleasure to make your
acquaintance.
Nice to meet you.
-(ALL LAUGHING)
-JEAN JACQUES: It's a joke.
You'll understand
when you're in the fucking seat.
You need a bigger couch. For
guests.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I don't understand. I'm sorry.
I'm curious about
your bank secrecy laws here.
Wait. Yes. Excusez-moi, Jordan.
Swiss custom requires 10 minutes
of...
Blah, blah, blah.
-Chit chat.
-Yeah, chit chat, thank you.
...before business can be
discussed.
Yeah.
Of course.
Let's get down to it.
What would you like to know?
Under what circumstances
would you be obligated
to cooperate with an FBI
or a U.S. Justice Department
investigation, for example?
Ça dépend.
-Ça dépend?
-Oui.
Ça dépend on what, exactly?
Whether America plans to invade
Switzerland
-in the coming months.
-(LAUGHTER)
Shall I check if tanks
are rolling down the Rue de la
Croy?
-Yes. Rue de la Croix.
-Croix. Croix.
Not Croy. Not Rue de la Croy.
It's Croix.
See, this is what he used to do
back in law school. Check me.
-Champagne. Champagne.
-Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. French fries, pommes
frites.
And that kind of stuff.
That's funny.
JORDAN: What I'm asking, you
Swiss dick,
is are you going to fuck me
over?
JEAN JACQUES: I understand
perfectly, you American shit.
The only way the Banque Réal de
Genève
would cooperate with a foreign
legal body
is if the crime being pursued
is also a crime in Switzerland.
But there are very few Swiss
laws
which apply to your practices.
Hmm.
From a financial standpoint,
you are now in heaven.
See, I told you he was
fantastic, right?
If the U.S. Justice Department
sent us a subpoena, it would
become
papier toilette.
We would wipe our ass with it.
(LAUGHTER)
Unless, of course, it was an
investigation
into stock fraud,
which is a crime here in
Switzerland,
if I'm correct.
Then there would
have to be coopération on your
part,
-if I'm not mistaken.
-Yes.
Yes, we would.
Assuming the account is under
your name.
If it were another name,
a friend's, camarade...
-Cousin?
-(AGREEING IN FRENCH)
-Relative?
-JEAN JACQUES: Yeah.
Hmm.
JORDAN: Was that yodeling I just
heard
or did you just say what I
thought you said?
JEAN JACQUES: Yes. Yes.
JORDAN: He's telling me to
use a fucking rathole.
But a U.S. rathole would never
get
into Switzerland with all that
money.
What I needed was a rathole
with a European passport.
Jordan.
Hey. How's my favorite aunt,
huh?
Welcome. Was the traffic
terrible?
Oh, no, not at all.
Jordan, come in.
Thank God Aunt Emma
didn't need too much convincing.
Turned out the British
weren't too different from the
Swiss.
Money talks and bullshit takes
the bus.
How do you say "rathole" in
British?
If you get into any trouble
whatsoever,
I'll come forth immediately.
I'll say that I duped you.
That I promise.
Risk is what keeps us young,
isn't it, darling?
Sometimes I wonder
if you let money get the best of
you, my love.
Among other substances.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
It's that obvious, huh?
It's chilly, darling,
and you're sweating bullets.
What can I say? I'm...
I'm a drug addict.
I really am.
Cocaine, pills,
whatever it is, I'll fucking do
it.
(CHUCKLES)
Now that's the truth.
I mean...
I'm a sex addict, too.
Well, there are worse things
to be addicted to than sex.
(LAUGHS)
Jesus, why am I telling you all
this?
Why am I...
I'm sorry.
Because I'm very easy to talk
to.
-You are. You are easy to talk
-Mmm.
I suppose it's...
Just my job, you know.
All these people dependent on
me.
Tens of millions of dollars at
stake, you know.
Sometimes I feel like I...
I've bitten off more than I can
chew,
you know.
You're a man with large
appetites.
Yeah.
JORDAN: Is she fucking hitting
on me?
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
I suppose I put that on myself
though, right?
My decision.
It's just hard to...
Hard to learn to control
the anxiety sometimes, you know?
You know, to...
Learn to relax and let go and...
To release the tension.
JORDAN: She is hitting on me.
Holy shit!
Yeah, to release the tension.
I suppose we...
We all just need to learn...
Learn to do what comes naturally
in life,
you know?
EMMA: Is he fucking hitting on
me?
Stability, dear.
Family.
You take care of my niece, my
love.
I'll take care of everything
over here.
Deal.
JORDAN: (MOANING) Come on! There
you go.
Whoo!
JORDAN: We had, literally,
a fuckload of money.
Aunt Emma could never
carry all this by herself.
So I thought to myself,
who else has a European
passport?
Brad, you're making this too
fucking tight!
Now Brad, as a successful drug
dealer,
spent his winters in the south
of France,
which is where he met his wife,
Chantalle,
a stripper of Slovenian origin
born, in of all places,
Switzerland.
Well, this is fucked.
Oh. No shit.
Like, this will take her like 50
trips.
I know.
Let me ask you something?
What about her family? Right?
I mean, they all got Swiss
passports, right.
She's got parents, she's got a
brother, right?
The brother's got a wife.
That's five fucking people.
Six, seven trips, boom, right?
They're all fucking Swiss
nitwits like her.
-They'll do it.
-We could do that.
At least I have a family,
you crooked-nose fuck!
Hey, don't forget about my
money.
I'm sorry, what's that?
Yeah, I forgot to tell you. He's
got some...
He's got some money.
My money.
I got a couple of mil coming in
like a week.
When it gets in,
I'll give you a call, you come
pick it up.
You give me a call?
When it gets here,
I'll give you a call and you'll
come pick it up.
Well, we don't fucking work for
you, man!
-(SHUSHING)
-DONNIE: Sweetheart,
you have my money taped to your
tits.
Okay? Technically, you do work
for me.
Hey, Jordan, we're gonna need to
talk.
If I fucking do this, I'm
telling you right now,
I ain't going to him, okay.
-I'm not a fucking shvartze.
-I got it.
I don't do fucking pickups, all
right?
-I got it.
-Well, listen to me.
We meet someplace that I fucking
say.
And you tell that fucking piece
of shit,
-he comes correct.
-I will.
He comes in all fucking loopy
and fucked up,
I swear to God
I'll mash that douchebag's teeth
in.
You're gonna mash whose fucking
teeth in?
Whose fucking teeth are you
gonna mash in?
I put the money on that fucking
table!
Not you!
I'm the reason
we have this whole fucking deal!
-He's got a gun, you fucking
idiot!
-Fuck his gun!
I put that money in there!
You know what? You're a fucking
pill dealer.
I got five more just like you,
bro.
Keep talking, you fucking piece
of shit!
You know what else? You dress
like shit!
So fuck you!
-Fucking motherfucker!
-Oh! Jesus!
How about that, faggot? Who's a
faggot?
JORDAN: You okay? Hey, pal.
JORDAN: The next day,
Aunt Emma flew to Geneva.
Two million in cash in her
carry-on,
which in the big picture
was a drop in the Swiss bucket.
'Cause the following month,
over the course of six round
trips,
Chantalle's family and
friends smuggled in over 20
million in cash
without even a hiccup.
(LAUGHS)
-And I have some more.
-Really?
-Here.
-Oh, thank you.
And here.
JEAN JACQUES: Welcome.
CHANTALLE: Welcome. (GIGGLING)
-Yeah, like four bags of it.
-Ooh!
(LAUGHS)
Are you Swiss-Slovakian or
Swiss-Slovenian?
-Slovenian.
-Slovenian?
Who cares. You're blonde.
Oh, stop.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Shit.
Just put the fucking car in
park,
you dumb fucking idiot!
I can't close this briefcase.
One fucking day.
One fucking day,
you couldn't keep it together?
I'm fucked up, Brad.
Gotta be fucking kidding me.
Fucked up.
-It's a joke.
-It's a joke?
-I'm sober.
-Jesus fucking Christ!
It's a fucking joke.
-Are you fucking stupid?
-I'm not stupid.
You fucking drive in here
like a fucking maniac,
you know the attention that
that fucking draws?
I'm not stupid. I'm smart.
Smart?
-I make million-dollar deals.
-That right?
With smart important people,
unlike you.
People who don't sucker-punch
people when they're scared.
Okay?
-I'm scared, huh?
-And by the way,
I haven't gotten an apology yet
for that.
You want an apology, okay.
I check my fucking messages
every day
-when I come home from work.
-Did you?
-My answering machine. Zero.
-Didn't get one, huh?
I got a blinking light,
because I don't have shit from
you.
You know what, you got
a big fucking mouth, okay?
I got my wife checking the
messages
every 45 minutes calling the
office, saying,
"Has Brad apologized yet?
"Is there an apology message
on the machine?"
I don't have jack shit. You know
what?
That's not how you treat people.
You got a big fucking mouth, you
know.
I'm gonna give you a fucking
pass.
Just give me the case.
(SCOFFS) You're gonna give me a
pass?
Look, it's a figure of fucking
speech.
Oh, my gosh. The Emperor of
Fucksville
came down from Fucksville to
give me a pass!
From Fucksville, huh?
Hey, what are the citizens
of Fucksville doing today
when their Emperor's gone?
Is it mayhem?
Are people looting and raping?
What are all
the little fuckheads doing while
you're here?
Go fuck yourself! Give me the
bag.
You back the fuck up.
I'll cause the biggest fucking
scene
that I've ever caused in my life
if you come at me again.
-You know what?
-Just fucking keep it down.
I got...
I don't wanna be out of line or
anything,
but I think you like, like me.
Like you...
Like when you come at me...
What's the matter with you?
What the fuck is...
...and you look at me. I swear I
just noticed it.
You have like a fucking, like...
Like a twinkle. You have like a
twinkle.
Are you trying to kiss me, bro?
Jesus fucking Christ.
-What's with you?
-I have a... I don't know.
-It's not a homophobic thing.
-All right...
You're just not the one for me,
pal.
You know what I mean? It's
not...
-It's not about that for me, you
know.
-I've heard enough.
Please, I'm begging, give me the
fucking case.
-I'm gonna give you the case.
-Give me the case.
-You gotta do me one favor.
-What's that?
You gotta take this case,
you gotta drive straight home,
need you to open up the
briefcase,
and you take out every single
dollar.
Don't leave one dollar inside
the briefcase.
And once you have it all
neatly organized outside the
briefcase,
I need you to take it
and I need you to shove it right
up
your wife's Latvian cunt, you
understand?
-My fucking wife!
-Chill! Chill, bro.
Fuck. You motherfucking piece of
shit!
-How about now?
-(SIREN WAILING)
DONNIE: Go, go!
BRAD: Fuck!
(ENGINE STARTING)
Motherfuck! You're fucking dead!
Stop! Don't move! Don't move!
Stop, or I will blow you the
fuck away!
Drop the case! Put your hands in
the air!
-Get down.
-(SCREAMS)
Get down on your knees!
Motherfucker!
Jordan, do I have a surprise for
you!
-What's that?
-Twenty real Lemmons.
Retired pharmacist's client of
mine,
they've been in the safe for 15
years.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Lemmons?
Ha-ha!
DONNIE: They're gonna knock us
on our fucking heads.
JORDAN: When it comes to
Quaaludes,
the Lemmon 714 was the Holy
Grail.
-Can you believe it?
-Oh, my God.
DONNIE: I thought they were like
a myth.
JORDAN: Three times
as powerful as anything
available today.
JORDAN: Look at these babies.
Boy, Donnie really knew how to
celebrate.
He said he was saving these
for a special occasion.
Like a birthday, or being clap
free,
or our money arriving safely in
Switzerland.
(RETCHES)
So that night,
I cleared my schedule and I rid
my body
of anything that could fuck with
my high.
It was celebration time.
Okay.
Start off with one, see how it
goes?
My guy says all we'll need is
one.
Here you go.
-Salud!
-Cheers.
Maybe if I pull it again, it'll
go down.
Steve! Steve!
I gotta get out of here!
Carl, I think I got it figured
out.
It must be one pull for up
and two pulls for down.
Okay.
Do you feel anything?
No.
It's been 35 minutes.
Hmm.
Maybe we've built up a tolerance
after all these years, huh?
Hmm.
DONNIE: This is bullshit!
My metabolism's pumping. I can't
feel shit!
They're old.
You think they lost their
potency, huh?
Check the bottle!
January '81.
-They're fucking duds.
-Fuck!
Let's take... Let's take two
more each.
NAOMI: Jordan.
Yeah, baby.
What are you two retards doing?
We're working out, honey.
Well, Bo Dietl's on the phone.
Okay.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Hey, Bo, what's going on?
Jordan, listen to me clearly.
I cannot talk to you on this
phone,
I have to talk to you.
Get out of here. What's going
on?
Listen to me!
Leave the fucking house, Jordan,
and then call me from a pay
phone.
This is not a fucking joke,
Jordan.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
-Shit.
-What'd he say?
I don't know what the fuck's
going on.
-I gotta go!
-Is everything okay, Jordan?
JORDAN: The closest pay phone I
could get to
was at the Brookville Country
Club.
It was a real WASP stronghold,
just a mile down the road from
my house.
Hey, Bo, what's up, it's me.
What's going on?
I'm at a pay phone. What's going
on?
Listen to me carefully.
Please. Your little friend
there, Brad,
your little buddy, he's in jail.
What the fuck's he in jail for?
-What'd he do?
-I don't know what he did.
My friends in Long Island told
me
he got picked up
in some fucking shopping mall.
He got locked up by...
Wait, wait. Did you...
Did you say a shopping mall?
-Yeah.
-He was with Donnie.
He was supposed to deliver some
money,
-then that fucking fat piece of
shit...
-Listen to me!
I gotta go fucking talk to him
right now!
Listen to me! Don't go! Listen
to me.
That guy Denham, that FBI agent
guy,
somebody told me
he's got your phones tapped.
Your office and your home.
Don't talk on the motherfucking
phone!
Okay. Fuck! I got it. I got it.
I got it.
Jordan.
You didn't try to bribe
this fucking FBI agent, did you?
No, I didn't try to bribe an FBI
agent.
You think I'm that fucking
stupid? No.
What the fuck did you say?
I can't understand you.
Say that again.
I said...
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
What the fuck are you saying?
(PANTING)
I said...
Are you fucking high?
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
Jordan, are you fucking high?
Jordan, do me a favor, stay
where you are.
Don't get behind the wheel of
the car.
I'm gonna send Rocco over to
pick you up.
Jordan! Jordan!
JORDAN: After 15 years in
storage,
the Lemmons had developed a
delayed fuse.
It took 90 minutes
for these little fuckers to kick
in.
But once they did...
Pow!
I mean, I had skipped the tingle
phase
and went straight to the drool
phase.
BO: Tell me where you are!
Don't fucking drive...
JORDAN: These little
bastards were so strong,
I discovered a whole new phase.
The cerebral palsy phase.
Come on, stand up!
Okay, walking's out.
All right, think, think. What
else is there?
Yes! I can crawl. I can crawl
like Skylar!
(GRUNTS)
Fuck! The kid makes it look so
goddamn easy!
Think, you motherfucker, think!
Yes!
I got it! I've got it!
I can roll! I can roll!
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
(MOANING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Ah!
(JORDAN YELLING)
NAOMI: Jordan.
(JORDAN YELLS)
Jordan.
Oh, Jesus. Where are you?
(SLURRING) I'm at a country
club!
What?
I'm at a country club!
I don't know what the fuck
you're saying.
Look, you need to get home.
Donnie is out of control!
He's on the other line
with some Swiss guy. I don't
know...
What?
Get him off the phone!
I can't understand you!
Get him
off
the phone!
I don't know what the fuck
you're saying, Jordan.
Can you just get home? Hurry!
(JORDAN YELLING GIBBERISH)
(SOBBING)
JORDAN: I was less than a mile
from home.
I drove as slow as I fucking
could.
I'd seen Jell-O move faster.
DONNIE: (SLURRING)
I was gonna give you two
million.
I's gonna be lates.
You ate two million?
Later.
JORDAN: Get off the phone.
Get off the fucking phone!
Idiot!
(CAR HONKING)
MAN: Get out of the way,
asshole!
(DONNIE SPEAKING GIBBERISH ON
PHONE)
You hate two million?
No, you don't hate two million,
Donnie.
JORDAN: By some miracle,
I made it home alive,
not a scratch on me or the car.
(GRUNTING)
-(DONNIE MUMBLING)
-(TV PLAYING)
-NAOMI: Jordan?
-(SCREAMS)
Jesus fucking Christ!
What did you take?
What's wrong with you?
Jor!
It's fucking good, right?
Fucked up!
(LAUGHS)
Get off the phone!
What the fuck, Jordan?
Your daughter's in the house!
I hope you know that!
Your fucking daughter's in the
house!
-(DONNIE LAUGHING)
-Yeah, it's real fucking funny,
Donnie.
Get off the phone!
-(LAUGHS)
-NAOMI: Jesus Christ, Jordan.
The FBI!
Hey!
I'm on phone!
Get off the fucking phone!
-Come here!
-...the phone.
NAOMI: Come on.
We're gonna go upstairs, all
right.
Ow!
I'm on the phone!
On the phone!
I know what you did,
you piece of shit!
What? What?
Brad!
You fucking cocksucker!
(SCREAMS)
What did you do,
you piece of shit?
Fuck you!
I wanna fucking kill you!
I got you!
(GROANS)
(MOANING)
(COUGHS)
(CHOKING)
What the fuck happened?
Oh, shit!
Jordan? Jordan, are you all
right?
Donnie? Donnie?
Donnie?
Jordan, he's not breathing.
Oh, fuck, I don't know what to
do.
Jordan, I don't know what the
fuck to do!
I can't help him! Oh, my God.
Jordan.
Oh, my God, I think he's
choking, Jordan.
Do something.
-Oh, God.
-JORDAN: Baby, I got you!
He's not breathing, Jordan.
You gotta do something!
Shit! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
OLIVE OYL: Ah!
I got you.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(INHALING)
Oh!
Step aside!
Oh, God!
Move aside, baby.
(JORDAN GRUNTING)
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
(CHOKING)
Jordan, he's not breathing.
You gotta do something.
Jordan, he's a father! He's got
fucking kids!
-Do something!
-Yeah?
(BLOWING)
(GRUNTS)
NAOMI: Rocco, you gotta get over
here.
-Come on.
-Call an ambulance!
I don't fucking know!
Just get over here! Call 911.
(GASPING)
(YELLING)
Yeah.
You all right? He's all right.
POLICE OFFICER: Mr. Belfort?
Mr. Belfort?
JORDAN: Get the fuck out of
here. Fuck.
(COUGHS)
Sir, we need to ask you some
questions.
Are you fucking kidding me? Fuck
you.
POLICE OFFICER: Come on, get up.
Get the fuck out of my house.
-Let's go.
-I've been here all night.
I been sitting here all night.
What the fuck are you talking
about?
-Where you taking him?
-Where you taking me?
-You ain't got no warrant.
Just come up in people's house
like that!
Did you drive your car tonight,
Mr. Belfort?
Huh?
Well?
JORDAN: Wow!
Maybe I hadn't made it home
okay.
Get out of the fucking way!
Fuck!
POLICE OFFICER:
Did you drive that car tonight?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, right.
I'm a family man!
Family man. Honey!
It was a miracle I wasn't
killed,
or that I didn't kill anybody
else.
The cops took me in for
questioning,
but they couldn't charge me.
They had no proof
I was even behind the wheel.
Meanwhile,
Brad did three months in jail
for contempt
because he wouldn't rat Donnie
out.
The result, I was scot-free.
But I had eyes on me like never
before.
MANNY: You're a lucky man,
Jordan.
You're lucky to be alive, let
alone not in jail.
You know I don't believe in
luck, right?
But it's time.
Please, let me call the SEC and
cut a deal
before your luck runs out.
NAOMI: Wave to Daddy.
Hey.
Hey, sweetie.
(CHUCKLES)
What kind of terms
would you be talking about if
I...
MANNY: I don't know.
You plead guilty to a handful
of securities violations,
stock manipulation,
high-pressure sales tactics.
Ticky-tack shit like that, you
know.
You pay a couple million dollars
in fines,
in exchange, the SEC
fucks off till the end of time.
And Stratton?
What happens to Stratton?
There's no way... I mean...
You got to walk away. Right?
Let Donnie be in charge.
Right. Donnie.
Now the FBI is another animal
completely.
They'll still be
pursuing you for criminal
wrongdoing.
However, with you stepping down
voluntarily,
my guess is that
your best friend Agent Denham
will be standing around
with his dick in his hand.
MAX: Jordan.
What do you have to think about?
You beat them.
You won!
God knows you never have to work
again.
MAX: What're you gonna do?
Spend the rest of your life in
jail?
-Is that what you want?
-JORDAN: No.
-Of course not.
-Okay.
Okay! You got all the money in
the world.
You need everybody else's money?
-Of course not, Pops.
-Well?
-You know, I built it.
-I know you built it.
You built it, so now preserve
it.
(ALL MURMURING)
(APPLAUDING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
You know,
five years ago,
when I started Stratton Oakmont
with Donnie Azoff, I knew the
day
would eventually come
where I'd have to be moving on.
(SIGHS)
And it's truly
with a heavy heart that I'm here
to say that...
That that day is finally here.
(ALL MURMURING)
I wanna... I want to thank you
all for your...
Your years of loyalty and
admiration.
But the point is this.
Under Donnie's leadership,
along with Nicky Koskoff
and Robbie Feinberg
moving into key management
positions,
this place really
is gonna be better than ever!
That I promise you. Okay?
Give them a round of applause.
Come on.
This is Ellis Island here,
people.
I don't care who you are, where
you're from,
whether your relatives
came over on the fucking
Mayflower
or on an inner tube from Haiti,
this right here is the land of
opportunity.
Stratton Oakmont is America!
All of you know Kimmie Belzer,
right?
-WOMAN: Yes, we do.
-(MEN WHISTLING)
Fuck you.
-(ALL LAUGH)
-Come on, Kimmie.
What you probably didn't know
is,
Kimmie was one of the first
brokers here,
one of Stratton's original 20.
Now most of you met Kimmie,
the beautiful sophisticated
woman
that she is today.
A woman that wears $3,000 Armani
suits.
(CHUCKLES)
Who drives a brand-new
Mercedes-Benz.
A woman who spends
her winters in the Bahamas
and summers in the Hamptons!
That's not the Kimmie that I
met.
The Kimmie that I met
didn't have two nickels to rub
together.
She was a single mom on the
balls of her ass
with an eight-year-old son.
Okay? She was
three months behind on her rent.
And when she came to me
and asked me for a job,
she asked for a $5,000 advance
just so she could pay her son's
tuition.
And what'd I do, Kimmie?
Go on, tell them.
You wrote me a check
for $25,000.
That's right.
Thank you.
And you know why that is?
It's because I believed in you.
It's because I believed in you,
Kimmie,
just like I believe in
each and every one of you here
today.
I fucking love you, Jordan!
I fucking love you.
I fucking love you! I love you.
I fucking love you, too!
And I love all of you!
And I love all of you
from the bottom of my heart.
I fucking love you, too.
I mean that.
You are the shit. You are the
fucking shit.
It's a shame, you know.
For years, I've been telling you
guys
never to take no for an answer,
right?
You know, to keep pushing,
to never hang up the phone
until you get what you want.
Because you all deserve it.
You know, this fucking deal
that I'm about to sign
barring me from the securities
industry,
barring me from Stratton,
my home.
What the fuck is that, you know?
I'll tell you what it is.
It's...
It's me taking no for an answer,
you know.
It's them...
It's them selling me,
not the other way around.
It's me being a hypocrite is
what it is.
So...
You know what?
I'm not leaving.
(ALL MURMURING)
I'm not fucking leaving!
(ALL CHEERING)
You're not getting a fucking
promotion!
The show goes on!
This is my home!
They're gonna need a fucking
wrecking ball
to take me out of here!
They're gonna need to
send in the National Guard
or fucking SWAT team
'cause I ain't going nowhere!
Fuck them!
(HUMMING)
(ALL HUMMING)
Jordy! Jordy!
Jordy! Get back here!
Hey!
Give me that.
(CAWING)
MAX: What is this?
Ramar of the Jungle, for Christ
sake?
MAN: (ON PHONE) Paddy D,
mazel tov, you Irishman.
Jordan Belfort just welched
on his deal with the SEC.
He is back in the ocean. Happy
hunting.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
JORDAN: It was our time to party
big.
And just as Brad was released
from jail, too.
I apologized, even offered
to pay him for his time in the
can.
But he said no, that he was out.
He didn't want any part of us.
Sad thing was,
two years later he was dead.
Massive heart attack.
Thirty-five.
Same age Mozart died.
Not that they have a hell
of a lot in common, but...
Anyway, I don't know why that
came to mind.
Within days, subpoenas started
flying.
Notices to produce documents,
depositions, you name it.
Donnie couldn't drink water fast
enough.
DONNIE: United States
government wants to give me a
subpoena?
Here's what we do
with subpoenas at Stratton
Oakmont!
Fuck you, USA! Fuck you!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
ALL: (CHANTING) Fuck you!
Jordan Belfort.
ATTORNEY: Alden. That's a nice
name.
Thank you very much for that.
-What kind of name is that?
-That is my name.
I do not recall that.
I do not recall that. Okay?
ATTORNEY: Mr. Ming,
thank you for coming in today.
Are you gonna finish the rest of
that Danish?
-Can I have that Danish?
-No, no, go ahead.
JORDAN: They interrogated
everybody.
I got a low blood sugar, thyroid
thing.
JORDAN: It went on for months.
It was a total fucking
harassment.
Tell him to proceed with the
questions.
JORDAN: But not a single
Strattonite cracked.
ATTORNEY: Gladys Carrera?
Doesn't ring a bell.
Sorry, I have no recommendation
of that.
-No.
-No idea.
I don't recall that transaction.
You guys have any milk?
Absolutely not.
ATTORNEY: Francis Sortigi
you called so many times
I just thought you might
remember that.
Would you remember any of those?
-I do not recall any of that.
-This Abdul...
I do not... No, I don't recall.
ATTORNEY: It was a long phone
call.
I just wondered if you have
any memory of that.
Okay. You know we've
talked to several of the
employees at this firm
and nobody can recall anything
about this Steve Madden IPO.
I think it's odd.
MANNY: Do you recall Cartage
Corporation?
Mmm.
You do recall it?
No, I don't recall that at all.
Excuse me. I have to ask.
Is that your real hair?
Are you gonna say anything about
that?
Are you gonna comment on my
hair?
Is that how we're doing...
Is this personal questions?
I'm just wondering why you
would wear something like that.
Sorry. I don't recall that
company.
Can I get you anything else,
gentlemen?
Yes. Sweetheart, I have a rare
condition
which requires me to drink one
of
those every 15 minutes, please.
JORDAN: We were
specifically advised not to
leave the country.
So, we took our wives to Italy.
We figured we were safer
working from overseas
giving orders to Rugrat.
Nobody could arrest us
and nobody could prove
I was still running Stratton
from a yacht.
Hey, Rugrat.
-Oh!
-Bonjour.
You bald-headed eagle, how you
doing?
NICKY: Donnie, Donnie, listen!
We have a problem, okay.
Your friend, Steve Madden,
is unloading shares.
What are you saying? Who told
you that?
-What's going on?
-He's doing it, Donnie!
He said that
Steve Madden's unloading shares.
Who told you that? It's
bullshit!
Give me that goddamn phone.
What's going on?
Jordan, look. I'm watching the
screen
and huge chunks
of Steve Madden are being sold,
okay.
It's not coming from us, so it's
gotta be Steve.
He's the only person with that
many shares.
It's Donnie. Call me back, all
right.
Donnie, your little friend
is trying to fuck me, you know
that.
Your little friend is
trying to fuck me right in the
ass.
-Get him on the phone now!
-We don't know anything yet.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
JORDAN: Even though I owned 85%
of Steve-cocksucking-
motherfucking-Madden Shoes,
the shares were in his fucking
name.
This motherfucker knew
I was in trouble with the feds
and was trying to take
advantage.
Talk to me, man.
How do you wanna play this?
I want you to get
all our clients on the phone
right now
and have them start selling
Steve Madden.
We're gonna drive that fucking
price down!
Do you hear me? Shut the fuck
up!
This is your fucking friend from
high school.
If that little fucking prick
thinks he can fuck with me,
we'll turn his company into a
penny stock!
You hear me?
-You got it?
-Yes. I got it!
DONNIE: Let's just not jump to
conclusions
before we know what's going on.
Captain Ted!
Hang up your phones! Everybody,
hey!
Turn the boat around! We're
going home!
(NAOMI SOBBING)
Baby! Baby, what happened?
I just...
Sweetheart, what's going on?
Aunt Emma...
Just wait.
I can't...
What's going on? Why you crying?
-She's dead!
-Who? Who's dead?
I just got a call from my cousin
Betty.
Yeah?
Aunt Emma is dead.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No.
You're serious?
Oh, my God! Baby, that's...
Oh, fuck!
Oh, sweetheart, that's just...
JORDAN: Fucking heart attack!
Boom, snap, gone.
Shuffled off her mortal coil.
And $20 million stuck
in a Swiss bank account.
The last time I talked to her
she was fine!
-She's not that old.
-Oh, God! Baby, oh, God!
That's so fucking terrible!
Oh, fuck!
It is terrible.
Your aunt was such an elegant,
attractive woman.
My condolences to you and your
family.
Yes. We're absolutely
devastated.
Thank you so much for your
condolences.
Now where does that
leave us in regard to her
account exactly?
Does it go into probate or what?
Not to worry, Jordan. Not to
worry.
Your aunt, before she died,
signed a document
naming you as her successor.
She did? (LAUGHS)
Fantastic! Well, that's good
news!
Well, not as of yet.
What does that mean? Not as of
yet?
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
I can't seem to hear you.
I must have bad reception.
Are you speaking English?
Very... Now. Fast. Very fast.
Fast?
I have to get to Switzerland
now?
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
Speak English! Fucking speak
English!
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey. Hey! Quiet,
okay?
Take your suit, take your dick,
okay,
-and move your ass! Please.
-Okay.
-(SPEAKING FRENCH)
-Move my ass! Yes!
I gotta say, these Swiss were
some sneaky motherfuckers.
Within minutes,
he had me set up with a forger
who could fake Aunt Emma's
signature.
You American shit!
I just had to get there by
tomorrow,
or lose $20 million.
We're going to Monaco!
Monaco? Now?
Yes, baby.
We're going to Monaco,
so then we can go to
Switzerland, okay?
-But her aunt just died.
-I realize that.
But I have business in
Switzerland.
I need to go to Switzerland
right now.
Bottom line. Sorry.
We gotta get to London.
Why? Why?
The funeral!
Yeah, but, babe. Look, look...
I loved your aunt
more than anyone in the entire
world.
I really did.
But she's dead now, sweetie.
She's dead and she's not going
anywhere.
She'll still be
dead by the time we get to
London, okay?
Captain Ted! Captain Ted, all
right, look.
We're going to Monaco. Monaco
now, okay?
Monaco, right.
We're going to Monaco
so that we can drive to
Switzerland
so they don't stamp our
passports.
Take care of business here,
we'll drive back to Monaco,
take a flight over to London
to catch the funeral
and be in New York
in three fucking business days!
That's the fucking plan.
I just want you to know that
we might run into some chop.
Chop? We can fucking handle
chop, right?
I mean, it's a 170-foot yacht.
No, no, no. We're not going
anywhere
unless he says it's safe, all
right.
-Don't worry about the chop.
-It's safe.
You don't know shit about chop.
Oh, really? And you do?
You're a fucking expert on that.
I'll chop your fucking credit
card in half.
How about that?
Chop is fine. Trust me. Chop is
fine.
Is chop fine, Captain Ted?
Uh...
Yeah. I mean, if we take it
slow.
Yeah, we're gonna take it slow.
It's a little uncomfortable.
Tell them it's safe.
CAPTAIN TED: It's gonna be safe.
We'll batten down the hatches
and secure the deck.
And we're looking at a few...
Maybe a few broken dishes.
Few broken dishes.
(LAUGHS)
What's a few broken dishes?
Does that sound fucking awesome
or what?
No. Not really.
We're gonna have a fucking good
time!
Let's go to fucking Monaco now!
Let's fucking move! Let's go!
(THUNDER CRACKING)
CAPTAIN TED: Hold on!
What the fuck is going on out
here?
The Jet Skis just went
overboard!
Oh, Jesus Christ! Honey, you
okay?
MAN: (OVER RADIO)
Gale warning! Gale warning!
CAPTAIN TED: The waves are
20 feet high and building!
Turn around, let's go the other
fucking way.
-CAPTAIN TED: We can't!
-Go!
We'll get broad-sided. It'll tip
over!
I am a master diver. You hear
that?
I'm a master diver!
No one's gonna fucking die!
I got you, baby. I got you.
Trust me, okay?
I love you.
I love you, baby. Just hold on
tight.
Okay.
Donnie!
Hold on, baby!
-What?
-Hold on, baby.
(WHISPERING) Get the fucking
ludes.
I don't wanna die, Jordan!
I did a lot of bad shit.
I'm going to hell, Jordan!
(SOBBING) I fucked up! I fucked
up so bad!
Get the ludes! Downstairs!
What are you saying?
Fuck!
Get the ludes!
I can't go down there, Jordan.
It's flooded.
It's three feet of water down
there!
I will not die sober!
Get those fucking ludes!
Okay!
-Go!
-Okay.
NAOMI: Where's he going?
JORDAN: Hold on, baby!
NAOMI: Donnie! Is he fucking
crazy?
JORDAN: He's just warning
everybody!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Jesus Christ!
Hold on!
Get away from the window!
Rogue wave!
Mayday!
This is Captain Ted Beecham
aboard the yacht Naomi!
-We are going down!
-I got 'em!
I got 'em!
Give me one for the nerves!
We're going down!
CAPTAIN TED: This is a fucking
Mayday!
We require immediate assistance!
-(SCREAMS)
-Hold on!
Watch out!
(PEPPY SONG PLAYING)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
JORDAN: The nice thing about
getting rescued by Italians
is that they feed you,
make you drink red wine,
then you get to dance.
Did you see that?
That was the plane I sent to
come get us.
I shit you not, it exploded when
a
seagull flew into the engine.
Three people killed.
You want a sign from God?
Well, after all this, I finally
got the message.
(INFOMERCIAL MUSIC PLAYING)
JORDAN: Do you dream
of becoming financially
independent
but struggle every month
just to pay your bills?
Would you like to own a home
like this,
but can barely afford to pay
your rent?
My name is Jordan Belfort,
and there's no secret to wealth
creation.
No matter who you are,
no matter where you came from,
you too can become financially
independent
in just a matter of months.
All you need is a strategy.
When I was 24 years old,
I made a decision not just to
survive,
but to thrive.
WOMAN: At first I didn't
feel like deals like these were
possible.
But we have the house
and we have a $33,000 profit.
I certainly believe now.
Think about it for a second.
If you don't have the guts
to attend Jordan Belfort's
Straight Line Persuasion System
seminar,
then how do you expect to make
any money?
JORDAN: If you want to be
a millionaire someday,
have some guts. Make a decision.
Jordan Belfort's setup
worked for me because I worked
hard for it.
And if it doesn't work for you,
it's because you're lazy.
And you should get a job at
McDonald's.
JORDAN: There's nobody
holding you back from financial
freedom.
And there's
nobody stopping you from making
millions.
Don't just sit at home,
or the life of your dreams
will sail right past you.
I changed all these people's
lives and I can change yours,
too!
So come to my seminar!
The life of your dreams is
only...
Good to see you again, Jordan.
You're under arrest!
You gotta be joking!
You're kidding me.
Hey, get the fuck away from me!
Turn that camera off.
JORDAN: I'm fucking shooting
a fucking infomercial here,
you fucking cocksucker!
-Fuck you, you motherfucker!
-Shut the fucking camera off.
You don't got shit on me, you
hear me!
Go fuck yourself!
I'm making an honest living,
you fucking piece of shit!
DENHAM: Hey, Jordan,
let me give you a little legal
advice.
Shut the fuck up!
JORDAN: Oh, fuck you, you
fucking prick!
I'm making an honest living,
you motherfucker!
JORDAN: I clean up my act.
I did rehab. I'm a TV
personality.
I'm sober for two years. And
this happens!
Rugrat goes and gets busted down
in Miami.
I'm Swiss, I'm not communist.
JORDAN: And guess
who the fuck with? Saurel.
-You gonna beat me?
-No, sir.
Yeah, I know your country.
You're gonna beat me.
JORDAN: I mean, what are the
fucking odds?
There had to be 10,000
Swiss bankers in Geneva,
and Rugrat gets the one dumb
enough
to get himself arrested on U.S.
soil.
I know.
(SOBBING) I'm so sorry.
Even more fucked
-was that he got busted
-(CAMERA CLICKING)
for shit that had nothing to do
with me.
It had nothing to fucking do
Something about laundering drug
money
through offshore boat racing
and a guy named Rocky Aoki,
you know, the founder of
Benihana.
Beni-fucking-hana!
(YELLING) Beni-fucking-hana!
Why?
Why, why, God?
Why would you be so cruel
as to choose
a chain of fucking hibachi
restaurants
to take me down?
Long story short. Saurel rats me
out.
But not before he rats out
Brad's wife, Chantalle,
who, it turns out, he'd been
fucking
every time she went to
Switzerland!
-No, no, no, it's impossible.
-Oui, oui, oui.
-All right!
-Ah! (GIGGLING)
JUDGE: One count engaging in
conspiracy
to commit securities fraud.
Two counts securities fraud.
One count engaging in
conspiracy to commit money
laundering.
Twenty-one counts money
One count obstruction of
justice.
Bail is set at $10 million.
DONNIE: Uncle Donnie's here!
Rocky. How you doing?
Woof. I hate that fucking dog.
Yeah, he's getting old and
decrepit.
Starting to shit in the house
again.
-Me, too.
-Come here, buddy.
Ah, fuck.
-It's good to see you, pal.
-Yeah, you, too.
Good to see you.
Sit down. Oh, man.
How you doing, brother?
(SIGHING) You know.
Shitty, pal.
But I'm hanging in there.
My new piece of jewelry. Check
that out.
Can't leave the house, you know?
Starting to get cabin fever
already.
Fucking Rugrat.
That wig-wearing faggot.
I can't believe that fucking
guy.
I wanna kill him.
Swear to God, I want to choke
him to death.
Irresponsible little prick.
-(SCOFFS)
-I'll tell you one thing.
I'm never eating at Benihana
again.
I don't care whose birthday it
is.
Where's Naomi? How's she doing?
That's her in the house there.
You could say hi,
but she probably won't wave
back.
Naomi, sweetheart!
What's up her ass?
-Is she mad at me?
-No, you know...
We probably have to mortgage the
house
in order to make bail.
Probably end up selling the
thing
in order to pay for all the
lawyers.
It's been a nightmare, buddy,
to tell you the truth.
What are you gonna do, right?
Anyway, how's Stratton?
That's more important.
How's morale?
They all pissed off
'cause they have to make money
legally now?
-Jordan.
-Hmm?
I got the founding partners
together.
I talked to them about
everything.
And I got you.
What do you mean, you got me?
The house, money, don't worry
about it.
I got you.
All right.
I love you, buddy.
-You know I'd do it for you,
right?
-I know.
-You know that, right?
I could fucking kiss you all
over.
All right, enough, enough.
(LAUGHING)
You want a beer, pal?
What are you drinking?
I got this non-alcoholic shit.
What's that?
A non-alcoholic beer. It's got
no alcohol.
It's a beer?
Yeah, with no alcohol.
But if you drink enough,
if you drink a lot, they get you
fucked up?
No, there's no alcohol.
That's the fucking point.
I'm not a scientist.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
I can get you a beer
if you want a fucking beer.
I know, but I don't drink. You
remember?
I don't drink anymore.
Oh, you wanna go inside
and blow some lines of baking
powder?
-Or baking soda...
-(CHUCKLING)
Can't imagine
ever not enjoying getting fucked
up.
-Yeah.
-I love it.
How's being sober?
-Fucking sucks.
-Boring, right?
So boring. I wanna kill myself.
There's a term, and we don't
like to use it
unless circumstances dictate,
and I think they do dictate in
this case,
and the term is "Grenada."
Have you ever heard of Grenada?
No. No, I haven't.
Grenada's very interesting
because it is a small island
nation
that was invaded by
the United States of America in
1983.
It's about 90,000 people.
And essentially, it means
this case is unloseable.
Okay?
So, you know, we can come in,
we can have our dick
hanging out of our pants.
Nobody gives a fuck.
I'm gonna win.
You, sir,
are what's known
-as a Grenada.
-JORDAN: Hmm.
You're looking at real prison
time.
Hmm.
Money laundering
can get you as much as 20 years.
And our case
couldn't be stronger if we
caught you
shoving cash in your mattress.
JORDAN: Is that right?
DENHAM: Hey, Jordan. Jordan.
Your rotting away in jail
till your kids get out of
college,
that's not our ambition here.
There's other people involved in
this, too.
We think they need
to see their day in court as
well.
Why do I sense there's an offer
in the air?
Look at him.
He's got a sense. What are you,
Kreskin?
Full cooperation.
He provides us with a
comprehensive list
of all the co-conspirators
spanning the last seven years,
and he also agrees to wear a
wire.
(CHUCKLING) Wait...
Did you just say "wear a wire"?
A wire. Mmm-hmm.
What does that mean?
You want me to rat? Is that it?
No, I want you to cooperate.
-No. You want me to rat, right?
-Yes. We want you to rat.
That's fucking exactly
what we want you to do. To rat.
JORDAN: How was Cristy's party?
NAOMI: Fine.
JORDAN: Good.
Babe, I spoke to the lawyers
again today.
I have some really, really great
news.
Mmm-hmm.
Turns out you're completely
off the hook, honey.
I know that already.
Right. Exactly.
You never did anything wrong
in the first place, right?
It turns out, all the FBI really
wants from me is to cooperate.
You know?
Turns out I have so much
information
about the stock market and Wall
Street,
I could save the government
years of heartache,
not to mention countless
dollars.
Mmm-hmm.
But it gets even better, babe.
Because if I do decide to
cooperate,
I might only be looking at four
short years,
in which case, you know,
we could start fresh, maybe sell
the house.
And any fines that I'd have to
pay
wouldn't be due till after I
serve my term,
so we'd still have plenty
of money left over, you know?
Mmm-hmm.
The only thing that
of course bummed me out a little
bit
is this whole idea of having to
give information about my
friends.
Like you said,
"There's no friends on Wall
Street." Right?
Right. Right. Exactly.
There's a silver lining to that,
too, honey.
Because they said eventually...
Eventually everyone's gonna have
to give information on this
case.
So, at the end of the day,
it might not even be a factor.
You know?
Well, that's good news. Right?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm really happy for you.
What do you mean, happy for me,
sweetheart?
You should be happy
for the both of us. Right?
-Yeah, right.
-All right.
Come here, baby.
Give me a kiss, sweetheart.
Jordan...
Oh, come on, baby.
I haven't made love to you in so
long. Please.
No. Jordan, stop it.
Come on, honey, please.
No! Jordan, stop it!
I've loved you since the moment
I saw you.
(MURMURING)
I fucking hate you, Jordan.
Get off me!
Baby... Don't do that.
You know how much I love you,
right?
Stop that, sweetie. Please.
You wanna fuck me, Jordan?
You wanna fuck me?
Good.
Go ahead.
Go ahead and fuck me.
I want you to fuck me real hard.
I want you to fuck me like
it's the last fucking time.
-Why are you moving like that?
-Come on.
Please hold still.
'Cause I want you to come for
me, baby.
Come on, babe.
Come for me, baby.
I want you to come for me
like it's the last fucking time.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Come on, baby. Come for me.
Come for me, baby.
Come on, baby.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, baby, come.
-You want me to come for you?
Yeah.
-Yeah!
Huh? You want me to come for
you?
Oh, God, baby. Yeah!
Oh, God.
(GRUNTING) Oh, God.
(GASPS)
Oh, God.
Jesus.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, baby.
That was so fucking great!
Oh, God!
That was the last time.
What do you mean, baby?
I mean that was
the last time we ever have sex.
What are you talking about?
I want a divorce.
What do you mean, you want a
divorce?
What's that supposed to mean,
you want a divorce?
Get off me! I want a divorce.
You just made love to me.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I don't love you anymore,
Jordan!
Oh, you don't love me?
You don't love me anymore, huh?
Well, isn't that
just fucking convenient for you!
Now that I'm under federal
indictment,
with an electronic bracelet
around my ankle,
now you decide you don't
fucking love me anymore.
-Is that right?
-No, no.
What kind of person are you?
Tell me.
You married me!
What the fuck is that supposed
to mean?
Jordan, this is how it's gonna
go.
I'm gonna take custody of the
kids.
If you agree to the divorce
right now,
-I will allow visitation.
-(SIGHING)
-Okay? Don't try to fight it.
-Oh, my God.
It'll save us both a lot of
money
and I got a feeling you're gonna
need it.
You're not taking my kids,
sweetheart.
You hear me?
I've already talked to the
lawyer.
He said even if you don't get
convicted,
I've got a good chance of
getting them.
I got news for you.
You're not fucking taking my
children,
you vicious fucking cunt, you!
Fuck you, you fucking bitch!
You're not fucking taking
my goddamn fucking kids!
You hear me? Fuck you!
You're not fucking taking my
fucking kids!
Fucking bitch!
(PANTING)
Fucking whore!
(MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Fucking bitch! Piece of shit
fucking whore!
(SNORTING)
(CHUCKLES) Look at yourself,
Jordan.
You're sick!
You're a sick man!
Fuck you!
I told you, you're not taking my
fucking kids!
You think I would let my kids
near you?
Look at yourself!
You know what my lawyer said?
My lawyer said that you're going
to prison for 20 years, Jordan.
Twenty fucking years!
You're never gonna see the kids
again!
You don't think I'm gonna see
my...
No, I'm not fucking letting you
near my kids!
You don't think I'm gonna see
my fucking kids again, huh?
Don't you fucking touch them!
Don't you fucking touch me!
Sweetheart? You're coming on a
trip
with Daddy, all right?
You're coming on a trip with
Daddy.
NAOMI: Don't you fucking touch
her, Jordan.
I swear to God, I will fucking
kill you!
It's all right, baby.
You and Daddy are gonna go
on a little trip together, okay?
-A little trip together.
-NAOMI: Violet!
Violet!
-Get the key! Get the key!
-VIOLET: I got it!
NAOMI: Jordan, you open this
fucking door
right now! Open the door!
Put your seat belt on.
There you go. Get your legs in.
I'm taking her with me!
I told you I'm taking her with
me,
-you fucking bitch!
-(GARAGE DOOR OPENING)
You're not gonna stop me!
We're going on a little trip,
honey.
No! No!
Get the hell out of here!
VIOLET: Leave that baby alone!
Violet! Garage door! Close it!
SKYLAR: Mommy!
-Get out of here!
-Open the fucking door!
-(ENGINE STARTING)
-SKYLAR: Mommy!
VIOLET: No!
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
Oh, Lord! Oh, my heavens...
Get the baby!
Naomi, get the baby!
-Mommy.
-Honey, it's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
VIOLET: Oh, Mr. Jordan has lost
his mind.
JORDAN: Baby...
NAOMI: It's all right, honey.
She all right?
Is she all right?
What's the matter with you?
LUCAS: Paragraph one.
The defendant shall plead guilty
to all counts of the indictment
currently pending against him
in the United States District
Court
for the Eastern District of New
York.
Paragraph two.
DENHAM: Talk normally.
LUCAS: The defendant
shall participate in undercover
activities...
DENHAM: Breathe normally.
...including wearing a recording
device,
also known as a wire...
After five minutes,
you'll forget you even have it
on.
...in conjunction with the
investigation...
Fucking brutal.
Quit your bitching.
Paragraph four.
The defendant must not commit,
or attempt to commit, any
further crimes.
Please. Let me just sign
the fucking thing already.
Thank you.
Just here?
That'd be good.
Thank you.
JORDAN: It wasn't even a choice.
For the next six hours, I came
up with a list.
Friends, enemies, business
associates.
Anybody who'd ever
known me or taken so much as a
stock tip.
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: (CHANTING) Wolfie! Wolfie!
Wolfie!
The first name on the list was
Donnie.
(HOWLING)
(DONNIE LAUGHING)
Jordan, do you know how good it
is
to have you back in this office?
It's not the same when you're
gone.
It's sad, you understand? It's
like...
That fucking Steve Madden, huh?
I can't...
Swear to God, I can't even think
about it.
Every time I think about him, my
blood boils.
I can't even say his name.
-I know.
-It's, like, disgusting.
I grew up with this guy
and he betrays me like that.
Ugh!
He ever get back to you about
that...
About that account?
You remember.
It was like four or five mil,
something like that, right?
He was supposed
to kick back four or five mil,
was it?
Actually, I was...
I was fucked up, Jordan,
-so I don't really remember.
-Yeah.
Yeah, right. Stupid.
Well, if he calls you,
you make sure and contact me,
okay?
-(STAMMERING) Yeah. Of course.
-Yeah.
Of course, yeah. No, of course.
You gonna eat
that last piece of yellowtail,
bud?
No, it's all yours.
Can I get this?
So, what else is...
Well, how's Naomi and
everything?
You know how it is.
She hates my fucking guts.
How's Hildy? Good?
She's still alive,
so my life is fucked, you know?
Yeah.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Mr. Jordan.
Mmm?
Mr. Jordan, you got a visitor.
What?
You've got a visitor.
(SIGHING DEEPLY)
I need you to get dressed.
Why? What the fuck's going on?
You're going to jail.
All right.
I'll get some clothes on.
We'll give you a hand with that.
Okay.
(DOOR BANGING OPEN)
FBI!
Everybody sit down. Put your
hands
where they can be seen, and shut
up!
Don't you fucking touch me.
Get your fucking hands off me!
Don't get out of your seats!
It's fucking Chanel!
(ALL CLAMORING)
JORDAN: I gave up everyone.
And in return,
I got three years in some
hellhole
in Nevada I'd never even heard
of.
Like my pops, Mad Max, had said,
"The chickens had come home to
roost."
Whatever the fuck that means.
LAWYER: I hope Your Honor would
agree
that Mr. Belfort has
distinguished himself
in terms of his cooperation.
Mr. Belfort has
helped the government win
convictions
of over two dozen serious
offenders
and helped them recover millions
of dollars
to be made available
for restitution to their
victims.
The sentence of the court
shall be 36 months in federal
prison.
Please remand the defendant.
LAWYER: I'm sorry.
(HANDCUFFS LOCKING)
That's okay.
JORDAN: I'm not ashamed to admit
it.
When we arrived at the prison,
I was absolutely terrified.
GUARD: Belfort, on your feet.
JORDAN: But I needn't have been.
You see, for a brief fleeting
moment,
I'd forgotten I was rich.
And I lived in a place
where everything was for sale.
Wouldn't you like to learn how
to sell it?
MC: So listen.
I've met some bad motherfuckers
in my life.
I'm talking about
rock stars, professional
athletes, gangsters.
I'm telling you, some real bad
motherfuckers.
But this guy, my good friend,
Mr. Jordan Belfort, is the
single
baddest motherfucker I have ever
met.
So I want you right now
to give a warm Auckland,
New Zealand welcome
for my good friend
and the world's greatest sales
trainer,
-Mr. Jordan Belfort!
-(APPLAUSE)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Thank you.
(SIGHING)
Sell me this pen.
It's, uh...
(STAMMERING)
It's an amazing pen.
For professionals, it's a...
Sell me this pen.
Well, it's a nice pen.
You can use the pen
to write down thoughts
from your life so you can...
Sell me this pen.
Well...
This pen works and
I personally love this pen...
(MELANCHOLY JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(MARK HUMMING)